{
	"description": "Find the longest word out of 5 given kanji",
	"deck": [
		{ "question": "世代風給生", "answers": [ "世代","せだい" ], "comment": "世代 (せだい): generation, the world, the age" },
		{ "question": "世体立心進", "answers": [ "立体","りったい" ], "comment": "立体 (りったい): solid body, three-dimensional object, multi-storey car park" },
		{ "question": "世作言力肉", "answers": [ "力作","りきさく" ], "comment": "力作 (りきさく): tour de force, painstaking piece of work, achievement" },
		{ "question": "世元器手作", "answers": [ "元手","もとで","手元","てもと" ], "comment": "元手 (もとで): funds, capital, stock\n手元 (てもと): at hand, on hand, nearby, close at hand, way of moving one's arms, skill, money at hand, pocket money, grip, handle" },
		{ "question": "世先手地集", "answers": [ "手先","てさき","先手","さきて","せんて" ], "comment": "手先 (てさき): fingers, underling, stooge, subordinate, pawn\n先手 (さきて, せんて): front lines, vanguard, first move (in go, shogi, etc.), moving first, person with the first move, forestalling, (seizing the) initiative" },
		{ "question": "世入番気大", "answers": [ "大気","たいき" ], "comment": "大気 (たいき): atmosphere" },
		{ "question": "世名立交本", "answers": [ "本名","ほんみょう","ほんめい" ], "comment": "本名 (ほんみょう, ほんめい): real name, real name" },
		{ "question": "世園学空芸", "answers": [ "園芸学","えんげいがく" ], "comment": "園芸学 (えんげいがく): study of horticulture" },
		{ "question": "世場実名女", "answers": [ "実名","じつめい","名実","めいじつ" ], "comment": "実名 (じつめい): real name\n名実 (めいじつ): in name and in reality, nominally and virtually, form and contents" },
		{ "question": "世徒草生集", "answers": [ "生徒","せいと" ], "comment": "生徒 (せいと): pupil" },
		{ "question": "世歩先大名", "answers": [ "大名","だいみょう" ], "comment": "大名 (だいみょう): daimyo (Japanese feudal lord), daimio" },
		{ "question": "世火道草身", "answers": [ "道草","みちくさ" ], "comment": "道草 (みちくさ): loitering on the way, wayside grass" },
		{ "question": "世物場実念", "answers": [ "実物","じつぶつ","みもの" ], "comment": "実物 (じつぶつ, みもの): real thing, original, actual, ornamental plant used primarily for the visual effect of its fruit" },
		{ "question": "世行肉牛番", "answers": [ "牛肉","ぎゅうにく","肉牛","にくぎゅう" ], "comment": "牛肉 (ぎゅうにく): beef\n肉牛 (にくぎゅう): beef cattle" },
		{ "question": "世音真身実", "answers": [ "真実","しんじつ","さな","さね" ], "comment": "真実 (しんじつ, さな, さね): truth, reality, truth, reality, truth, reality" },
		{ "question": "中年重発面", "answers": [ "中年","ちゅうねん","年中","ねんじゅう","ねんちゅう","ねんぢゅう" ], "comment": "中年 (ちゅうねん): middle-age, middle age, midlife, one's middle years\n年中 (ねんじゅう, ねんちゅう, ねんぢゅう): whole year, all year round, throughout the year, always, all the time, middle class (of a nursery school, etc.), whole year, all year round, throughout the year, always, all the time, middle class (of a nursery school, etc.), whole year, all year round, throughout the year, always, all the time, middle class (of a nursery school, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "中徒紙園白", "answers": [ "白紙","はくし","しらかみ" ], "comment": "白紙 (はくし, しらかみ): white paper, flyleaf, blank paper, clean slate, lack of prior opinion, positions, etc., scratch, beginning, white paper, flyleaf, blank paper, clean slate, lack of prior opinion, positions, etc., scratch, beginning" },
		{ "question": "中心面大念", "answers": [ "しんじゅう","しんぢゅう","ちゅうしん","心中","しんちゅう","中心","なかご" ], "comment": "心中 (しんじゅう, しんぢゅう): double suicide, lovers suicide, double suicide, lovers suicide\n中心 (ちゅうしん): center, centre, middle, heart, core, focus, pivot, emphasis, balance, -centered, -centred, -focussed, -oriented, centered on, focussed on\n心中 (しんちゅう): in one's heart, true motives, mind\n中心 (なかご): core, tang (of a sword, etc.), middle of a nest of boxes" },
		{ "question": "中白給生学", "answers": [ "中学生","ちゅうがくせい" ], "comment": "中学生 (ちゅうがくせい): junior high school student, middle school pupil" },
		{ "question": "中花面世記", "answers": [ "中世","ちゅうせい" ], "comment": "中世 (ちゅうせい): Middle Ages (in Japan esp. the Kamakura and Muromachi periods ), medieval times, mediaeval times" },
		{ "question": "中言色元歩", "answers": [ "中元","ちゅうげん","元中","げんちゅう" ], "comment": "中元 (ちゅうげん): 15th day of the 7th lunar month, (last day of) Bon lantern festival, mid-year gift, summer gift, Bon Festival gifts\n元中 (げんちゅう): Genchuu era (of the Southern Court) (1384.4.28-1392.10.5)" },
		{ "question": "事気明身合", "answers": [ "気合","きあい" ], "comment": "気合 (きあい): scream, yell, fighting spirit" },
		{ "question": "事流草見男", "answers": [ "見事","みごと" ], "comment": "見事 (みごと): splendid, magnificent, beautiful, admirable, praiseworthy act, feat, commendable deed, utter (esp. defeat), total, complete" },
		{ "question": "事牛時命声", "answers": [ "時事","じじ" ], "comment": "時事 (じじ): events of the day, current affairs" },
		{ "question": "事集進人作", "answers": [ "人事","じんじ","ひとごと" ], "comment": "人事 (じんじ, ひとごと): personnel affairs, human affairs, human resources, HR, other people's affairs, somebody else's problem, other people's affairs, somebody else's problem" },
		{ "question": "交体明実出", "answers": [ "実体","じったい" ], "comment": "実体 (じったい): substance, entity, object" },
		{ "question": "交内月重白", "answers": [ "月内","げつない" ], "comment": "月内 (げつない): by the end of this month" },
		{ "question": "交前楽発流", "answers": [ "交流","こうりゅう" ], "comment": "交流 (こうりゅう): (cultural) exchange, interchange, interaction, (inter-) mingling, (social, etc.) networking, intercourse, alternating current, AC" },
		{ "question": "交目前学意", "answers": [ "目前","もくぜん" ], "comment": "目前 (もくぜん): before one's very eyes, under one's nose, imminence, close at hand" },
		{ "question": "交真器分数", "answers": [ "真分数","しんぶんすう" ], "comment": "真分数 (しんぶんすう): proper fraction" },
		{ "question": "交間国牛念", "answers": [ "国交","こっこう" ], "comment": "国交 (こっこう): diplomatic relations" },
		{ "question": "人作夜格理", "answers": [ "人格","じんかく" ], "comment": "人格 (じんかく): personality, character, individuality" },
		{ "question": "人元進草大", "answers": [ "大人","おとな","だいにん","たいじん" ], "comment": "大人 (おとな, だいにん, たいじん): adult, adult, man of substance or virtue, gentleman, giant, adult" },
		{ "question": "人器実所本", "answers": [ "本人","ほんにん" ], "comment": "本人 (ほんにん): the person himself" },
		{ "question": "人国外安音", "answers": [ "外国人","がいこくじん" ], "comment": "外国人 (がいこくじん): foreigner, foreign citizen, foreign national, alien, non-Japanese" },
		{ "question": "人実本男日", "answers": [ "日本人","にほんじん","にっぽんじん" ], "comment": "日本人 (にほんじん, にっぽんじん): Japanese person, Japanese people, Japanese person, Japanese people" },
		{ "question": "人配芸夜草", "answers": [ "芸人","げいにん" ], "comment": "芸人 (げいにん): player, performer, actor" },
		{ "question": "代体肉徒紙", "answers": [ "肉体","にくたい" ], "comment": "肉体 (にくたい): the body, the flesh" },
		{ "question": "代新徒分風", "answers": [ "新風","しんぷう" ], "comment": "新風 (しんぷう): new style" },
		{ "question": "代歩白給理", "answers": [ "代理","だいり" ], "comment": "代理 (だいり): representation, agency, proxy, deputy, agent, attorney, substitute, alternate, acting (principal, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "代用草記肉", "answers": [ "代用肉","だいようにく" ], "comment": "代用肉 (だいようにく): meat substitute" },
		{ "question": "会前色見楽", "answers": [ "会見","かいけん" ], "comment": "会見 (かいけん): interview, audience" },
		{ "question": "会器事科分", "answers": [ "分科会","ぶんかかい" ], "comment": "分科会 (ぶんかかい): subcommittee, subworking group" },
		{ "question": "会実事肉水", "answers": [ "事実","じじつ","実事","じつごと","じつじ" ], "comment": "事実 (じじつ): fact, truth, reality\n実事 (じつごと, じつじ): fact, (a) truth, realistic portrayal of an ordinary event (by a wise man), fact, (a) truth, realistic portrayal of an ordinary event (by a wise man)" },
		{ "question": "会集外世術", "answers": [ "会集","かいしゅう","集会","しゅうかい" ], "comment": "会集 (かいしゅう): audience, assembly, meeting\n集会 (しゅうかい): meeting, assembly, gathering, congregation, convention, rally" },
		{ "question": "体命車写元", "answers": [ "車体","しゃたい" ], "comment": "車体 (しゃたい): body (of car), frame" },
		{ "question": "体歩前心記", "answers": [ "前記","ぜんき" ], "comment": "前記 (ぜんき): aforesaid, above-mentioned, said, above" },
		{ "question": "体牛記人夜", "answers": [ "人体","じんたい","じんてい","にんてい" ], "comment": "人体 (じんたい, じんてい, にんてい): human body, personal appearance, looks, personal appearance, looks" },
		{ "question": "体生物空明", "answers": [ "生物体","せいぶつたい" ], "comment": "生物体 (せいぶつたい): organism" },
		{ "question": "体科会牛気", "answers": [ "気体","きたい" ], "comment": "気体 (きたい): vapour, vapor, gas" },
		{ "question": "体進牛芸重", "answers": [ "体重","たいじゅう","重体","じゅうたい" ], "comment": "体重 (たいじゅう): body weight, one's weight\n重体 (じゅうたい): seriously ill, serious condition, critical state" },
		{ "question": "体雨番前内", "answers": [ "体内","たいない" ], "comment": "体内 (たいない): interior of the body" },
		{ "question": "作会芸空長", "answers": [ "会長","かいちょう" ], "comment": "会長 (かいちょう): president (of a society), chairman" },
		{ "question": "作元見楽器", "answers": [ "楽器","がっき","器楽","きがく" ], "comment": "楽器 (がっき): musical instrument\n器楽 (きがく): instrumental music" },
		{ "question": "作国春王肉", "answers": [ "王国","おうこく","国王","こくおう" ], "comment": "王国 (おうこく): kingdom, monarchy\n国王 (こくおう): king" },
		{ "question": "作王合写足", "answers": [ "合作","がっさく" ], "comment": "合作 (がっさく): collaboration, joint work" },
		{ "question": "作番牛物楽", "answers": [ "作物","さくぶつ","さくもつ" ], "comment": "作物 (さくぶつ, さくもつ): literary work, produce (e.g. agricultural), crops" },
		{ "question": "元新数立生", "answers": [ "新生","しんせい","生新","せいしん" ], "comment": "新生 (しんせい): rebirth, new birth, nascent\n生新 (せいしん): fresh, new" },
		{ "question": "元草心大雨", "answers": [ "大雨","おおあめ" ], "comment": "大雨 (おおあめ): heavy rain" },
		{ "question": "先人術記親", "answers": [ "先人","せんじん" ], "comment": "先人 (せんじん): predecessor, pioneer, ancestor" },
		{ "question": "先半名重進", "answers": [ "先進","せんしん" ], "comment": "先進 (せんしん): seniority, advance, leadership" },
		{ "question": "先文前格写", "answers": [ "前文","ぜんぶん" ], "comment": "前文 (ぜんぶん): preamble, the above statement" },
		{ "question": "先春道交強", "answers": [ "春先","はるさき" ], "comment": "春先 (はるさき): beginning of spring" },
		{ "question": "先格日実集", "answers": [ "先日","せんじつ" ], "comment": "先日 (せんじつ): the other day, a few days ago" },
		{ "question": "先記物声国", "answers": [ "先物","さきもの" ], "comment": "先物 (さきもの): futures" },
		{ "question": "先集名強合", "answers": [ "集合","しゅうごう" ], "comment": "集合 (しゅうごう): gathering, assembly, meeting, set" },
		{ "question": "入体身集王", "answers": [ "身体","からだ","しんたい","しんだい","しんてい" ], "comment": "身体 (からだ, しんたい, しんだい, しんてい): body, torso, trunk, build, physique, constitution, health, corpse, dead body, body, physical system, person, body, physical system, person, body, physical system, person" },
		{ "question": "入給学間重", "answers": [ "入学","にゅうがく" ], "comment": "入学 (にゅうがく): entry to school or university, matriculation, enrolment (in university, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "入芸所肉半", "answers": [ "入所","にゅうしょ" ], "comment": "入所 (にゅうしょ): admission (e.g. to a training institution, research establishment, social welfare facility, etc.), entrance, imprisonment, internment, confinement" },
		{ "question": "入草新重意", "answers": [ "新入","しんにゅう" ], "comment": "新入 (しんにゅう): newly arrived, newly joined, newly entered" },
		{ "question": "入雨明出親", "answers": [ "出入","しゅつにゅう" ], "comment": "出入 (しゅつにゅう): in and out, income and expenses, free associations, run of the house" },
		{ "question": "内中大歩面", "answers": [ "内面","ないめん","うちづら" ], "comment": "内面 (ないめん, うちづら): inside, interior, the face one presents at home" },
		{ "question": "内中文草歩", "answers": [ "文中","ぶんちゅう","中文","ちゅうぶん" ], "comment": "文中 (ぶんちゅう): in the document, Bunchuu era (of the Southern Court) (1372.4.?-1375.5.27)\n中文 (ちゅうぶん): Chinese language (written), Chinese literature" },
		{ "question": "内元給配人", "answers": [ "配給","はいきゅう" ], "comment": "配給 (はいきゅう): distribution (e.g. films, rice), rationing (e.g. food, gasoline), food ration" },
		{ "question": "内声紙身理", "answers": [ "身内","みうち" ], "comment": "身内 (みうち): relatives, one's family, friends, members of the same organization, followers, henchmen, one's whole body" },
		{ "question": "内年立徒記", "answers": [ "年内","ねんない" ], "comment": "年内 (ねんない): by the end of the year" },
		{ "question": "内物立流紙", "answers": [ "物流","ぶつりゅう" ], "comment": "物流 (ぶつりゅう): (physical) distribution, distribution of goods, logistics" },
		{ "question": "内行会車術", "answers": [ "車内","しゃない" ], "comment": "車内 (しゃない): inside a train, car, etc." },
		{ "question": "写器外国配", "answers": [ "外国","がいこく","そとぐに","国外","こくがい" ], "comment": "外国 (がいこく, そとぐに): foreign country, foreign country\n国外 (こくがい): outside the country" },
		{ "question": "写器雨肉用", "answers": [ "器用","きよう","用器","ようき" ], "comment": "器用 (きよう): nimble-fingered, dexterous, dextrous, skillful (with the fingers), skilful, handy, clever, shrewd, ingenious\n用器 (ようき): tool, instrument" },
		{ "question": "写大元世会", "answers": [ "大会","たいかい" ], "comment": "大会 (たいかい): convention, tournament, mass meeting, rally" },
		{ "question": "写大見半新", "answers": [ "大半","たいはん" ], "comment": "大半 (たいはん): majority, more than half, most (of), mostly, largely, mainly, predominately, nearly" },
		{ "question": "写大集強元", "answers": [ "強大","きょうだい" ], "comment": "強大 (きょうだい): mighty, powerful" },
		{ "question": "写女道代国", "answers": [ "国道","こくどう" ], "comment": "国道 (こくどう): national highway" },
		{ "question": "写新立用国", "answers": [ "国立","こくりつ","立国","りっこく" ], "comment": "国立 (こくりつ): national\n立国 (りっこく): founding of a nation" },
		{ "question": "写明科園真", "answers": [ "写真","しゃしん" ], "comment": "写真 (しゃしん): photograph, photo, picture, snapshot, snap, movie" },
		{ "question": "写王女園歩", "answers": [ "王女","おうじょ","おうにょ","女王","じょおう" ], "comment": "王女 (おうじょ, おうにょ): princess, princess\n女王 (じょおう): queen" },
		{ "question": "写白交地命", "answers": [ "白地","あからさま","しろじ","しらじ","はくち" ], "comment": "白地 (あからさま, しろじ, しらじ, はくち): plain, frank, candid, open, direct, straightforward, unabashed, blatant, flagrant, white background, blank, female virgin, white background, blank, female virgin, white cloth, empty land, empty lot, amateur (of a prostitute, etc)" },
		{ "question": "写進明力前", "answers": [ "前進力","ぜんしんりょく" ], "comment": "前進力 (ぜんしんりょく): driving power" },
		{ "question": "出中草番王", "answers": [ "出番","でばん" ], "comment": "出番 (でばん): one's turn" },
		{ "question": "出元用車新", "answers": [ "新車","しんしゃ" ], "comment": "新車 (しんしゃ): new car" },
		{ "question": "出内足間器", "answers": [ "出足","であし" ], "comment": "出足 (であし): turnout (of people), start (e.g. race, campaign, term of office), constant forward movement, initial charge, dash" },
		{ "question": "出大見長記", "answers": [ "長大","ちょうだい" ], "comment": "長大 (ちょうだい): very long, great length" },
		{ "question": "出強園新流", "answers": [ "流出","りゅうしゅつ" ], "comment": "流出 (りゅうしゅつ): discharge, outward flow, efflux, effluence, haemorrhage, hemorrhage, bleeding (e.g. ink into paper), leak of (private) information or pictures" },
		{ "question": "出手中面器", "answers": [ "中手","なかて","手中","しゅちゅう" ], "comment": "中手 (なかて): mid-season crops, mid-season rice, mid-season vegetables, metacarpus\n手中 (しゅちゅう): in one's hands, in one's control" },
		{ "question": "出科集中念", "answers": [ "集中","しゅうちゅう" ], "comment": "集中 (しゅうちゅう): concentration, convergence, centralization, integration, gathering together" },
		{ "question": "出雨親集人", "answers": [ "人出","ひとで" ], "comment": "人出 (ひとで): crowd, turnout" },
		{ "question": "分水歩作園", "answers": [ "水分","すいぶん" ], "comment": "水分 (すいぶん): water, liquid, fluid, moisture, humidity, sap, juice" },
		{ "question": "分番風半器", "answers": [ "半分","はんぶん","はんぷん" ], "comment": "半分 (はんぶん, はんぷん): half, half minute" },
		{ "question": "分身面牛発", "answers": [ "身分","みぶん","分身","ぶんしん" ], "comment": "身分 (みぶん): social position, social status\n分身 (ぶんしん): parturition, delivery, one's child, branch, offshoot, one's other self" },
		{ "question": "前中発白実", "answers": [ "中前","ちゅうぜん" ], "comment": "中前 (ちゅうぜん): front of center field, front of centre field" },
		{ "question": "前体名楽会", "answers": [ "前名","ぜんめい","名前","なまえ" ], "comment": "前名 (ぜんめい): one's previous name\n名前 (なまえ): name, full name, given name, first name" },
		{ "question": "前和写内学", "answers": [ "学内","がくない" ], "comment": "学内 (がくない): within the school" },
		{ "question": "前男命器写", "answers": [ "男前","おとこまえ" ], "comment": "男前 (おとこまえ): handsome man" },
		{ "question": "力交用火見", "answers": [ "火力","かりょく" ], "comment": "火力 (かりょく): heating power, steam power, firepower" },
		{ "question": "力前身歩真", "answers": [ "前身","ぜんしん" ], "comment": "前身 (ぜんしん): antecedents, ancestor, previous position, previous existence, predecessor organization, predecessor organisation" },
		{ "question": "力命時月体", "answers": [ "体力","たいりょく" ], "comment": "体力 (たいりょく): stamina, endurance, physical strength, resilience, resistance to disease, strength of an organization (e.g. profitability, productivity, economic clout, stability, growth potential)" },
		{ "question": "力場記明給", "answers": [ "明記","めいき" ], "comment": "明記 (めいき): clear writing, specification" },
		{ "question": "力安声空明", "answers": [ "声明","せいめい","しょうみょう" ], "comment": "声明 (せいめい, しょうみょう): declaration, statement, proclamation, sabdavidya (ancient Indian linguistic and grammatical studies), chanting of Buddhist hymns (usu. in Sanskrit or Chinese)" },
		{ "question": "半写場人気", "answers": [ "人気","にんき","ひとけ","じんき" ], "comment": "人気 (にんき, ひとけ, じんき): popularity, popular feeling, business conditions, sign of life, human presence, humanity, humaneness, prevailing mood of a locality, emotional climate of a district" },
		{ "question": "半器生強科", "answers": [ "半生","はんしょう","はんせい","生半","なまなか" ], "comment": "半生 (はんしょう, はんせい): half death, half a lifetime\n生半 (なまなか): halfway-done, mediocre, uncertain, half-hearted, half-heartedly, insufficiently" },
		{ "question": "半声王学科", "answers": [ "科学","かがく","学科","がっか" ], "comment": "科学 (かがく): science\n学科 (がっか): study subject, course of study, department (university, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "半火本心進", "answers": [ "本心","ほんしん" ], "comment": "本心 (ほんしん): true feelings" },
		{ "question": "半肉徒入前", "answers": [ "前半","ぜんはん","ぜんぱん" ], "comment": "前半 (ぜんはん, ぜんぱん): first half, first half" },
		{ "question": "半言身科牛", "answers": [ "半身","はんしん","はんみ" ], "comment": "半身 (はんしん, はんみ): half the body, half length, stance with legs in an L-shape, with one leg bent in front and other extended behind (martial arts, traditional theater)" },
		{ "question": "半集数記言", "answers": [ "半数","はんすう" ], "comment": "半数 (はんすう): half the number, haploid" },
		{ "question": "合中紙安立", "answers": [ "中立","ちゅうりつ","なかだち" ], "comment": "中立 (ちゅうりつ, なかだち): neutrality, break between the light meal and the actual serving of tea (during a formal tea ceremony)" },
		{ "question": "合春食数月", "answers": [ "月食","げっしょく" ], "comment": "月食 (げっしょく): lunar eclipse" },
		{ "question": "合術時給身", "answers": [ "時給","じきゅう" ], "comment": "時給 (じきゅう): hourly pay, hourly wage" },
		{ "question": "合身水器長", "answers": [ "身長","しんちょう","長身","ちょうしん" ], "comment": "身長 (しんちょう): height (of body), stature\n長身 (ちょうしん): tall figure, high stature" },
		{ "question": "名先長芸内", "answers": [ "芸名","げいめい" ], "comment": "芸名 (げいめい): stage name" },
		{ "question": "名声気草園", "answers": [ "名声","めいせい" ], "comment": "名声 (めいせい): fame, reputation, renown" },
		{ "question": "名日意気心", "answers": [ "心意気","こころいき" ], "comment": "心意気 (こころいき): spirit, disposition" },
		{ "question": "名日目写火", "answers": [ "名目","めいもく","みょうもく" ], "comment": "名目 (めいもく, みょうもく): name, title, appellation, (something) nominal, (under the) pretext (of), pretense, name, title, appellation, (something) nominal, (under the) pretext (of), pretense" },
		{ "question": "名牛命明集", "answers": [ "命名","めいめい" ], "comment": "命名 (めいめい): naming, christening" },
		{ "question": "命場足真年", "answers": [ "足場","あしば" ], "comment": "足場 (あしば): scaffold, scaffolding, foothold, footing, foothold (e.g. in business), foundation, base, convenience for transportation, convenience of access (by road or rail)" },
		{ "question": "命王花学元", "answers": [ "花王","かおう" ], "comment": "花王 (かおう): peony, king of flowers" },
		{ "question": "命術場所念", "answers": [ "場所","ばしょ","所場","しょば","ショバ" ], "comment": "場所 (ばしょ): place, location, spot, position, room, space, basho, wrestling tournament\n所場 (しょば, ショバ): place (to run a business, e.g. street stall), place (to run a business, e.g. street stall)" },
		{ "question": "命見肉科親", "answers": [ "肉親","にくしん" ], "comment": "肉親 (にくしん): blood relationship, blood relative" },
		{ "question": "命配徒日力", "answers": [ "命日","めいにち" ], "comment": "命日 (めいにち): death anniversary" },
		{ "question": "和交空車男", "answers": [ "空車","くうしゃ","からぐるま","あきぐるま" ], "comment": "空車 (くうしゃ, からぐるま, あきぐるま): empty conveyance, free taxi, parking lot with spaces available, empty conveyance, free taxi, parking lot with spaces available, empty conveyance, free taxi, parking lot with spaces available" },
		{ "question": "和言理風肉", "answers": [ "和風","わふう" ], "comment": "和風 (わふう): Japanese style, light wind, moderate breeze" },
		{ "question": "和雨手年生", "answers": [ "生年","せいねん","年生","ねんせい" ], "comment": "生年 (せいねん): the year of a person's birth, age\n年生 (ねんせい): pupil in ... year, student in ... year" },
		{ "question": "器王安女本", "answers": [ "王女","おうじょ","おうにょ","女王","じょおう" ], "comment": "王女 (おうじょ, おうにょ): princess, princess\n女王 (じょおう): queen" },
		{ "question": "器空本念場", "answers": [ "本場","ほんば" ], "comment": "本場 (ほんば): home, habitat, center, centre, best place, authentic, genuine" },
		{ "question": "器草面学年", "answers": [ "学年","がくねん" ], "comment": "学年 (がくねん): academic year, school year, year in school, grade in school" },
		{ "question": "器集国出日", "answers": [ "日出国","ひいずるくに","ひいづるくに","にっしゅつこく" ], "comment": "日出国 (ひいずるくに, ひいづるくに, にっしゅつこく): Land of the Rising Sun, Land of the Rising Sun, Land of the Rising Sun" },
		{ "question": "国先安親雨", "answers": [ "先安","さきやす" ], "comment": "先安 (さきやす): lower future quotations" },
		{ "question": "国内白代音", "answers": [ "国内","こくない","こくだい","くぬち","内国","ないこく" ], "comment": "国内 (こくない, こくだい, くぬち): internal, domestic, internal, domestic, internal, domestic\n内国 (ないこく): home country" },
		{ "question": "国意写人言", "answers": [ "国人","こくじん","くにびと","こくにん","くにうど","くにゅうど" ], "comment": "国人 (こくじん, くにびと, こくにん, くにうど, くにゅうど): indigenous person, inhabitant of a country, local, native, local lords and samurai, daimyo who did not leave his domains to meet the shogun in Kyoto (during the Muromachi period), indigenous person, inhabitant of a country, local, native, local lords and samurai, daimyo who did not leave his domains to meet the shogun in Kyoto (during the Muromachi period), indigenous person, inhabitant of a country, local, native, local lords and samurai, daimyo who did not leave his domains to meet the shogun in Kyoto (during the Muromachi period), indigenous person, inhabitant of a country, local, native, local lords and samurai, daimyo who did not leave his domains to meet the shogun in Kyoto (during the Muromachi period), indigenous person, inhabitant of a country, local, native, local lords and samurai, daimyo who did not leave his domains to meet the shogun in Kyoto (during the Muromachi period)" },
		{ "question": "国文学火世", "answers": [ "国文学","こくぶんがく" ], "comment": "国文学 (こくぶんがく): Japanese literature" },
		{ "question": "国王給流色", "answers": [ "王国","おうこく","国王","こくおう" ], "comment": "王国 (おうこく): kingdom, monarchy\n国王 (こくおう): king" },
		{ "question": "国用新学文", "answers": [ "国文学","こくぶんがく" ], "comment": "国文学 (こくぶんがく): Japanese literature" },
		{ "question": "国科紙目術", "answers": [ "科目","かもく" ], "comment": "科目 (かもく): (school) subject, curriculum, course" },
		{ "question": "国肉術声記", "answers": [ "肉声","にくせい" ], "comment": "肉声 (にくせい): natural voice (without a microphone)" },
		{ "question": "国記目学物", "answers": [ "国学","こくがく" ], "comment": "国学 (こくがく): study of (ancient) Japanese literature and culture, provincial school (under Japan's ritsuryo system and pre-Sui Chinese law)" },
		{ "question": "園分風紙作", "answers": [ "作風","さくふう" ], "comment": "作風 (さくふう): literary style" },
		{ "question": "園外代時元", "answers": [ "時代","じだい" ], "comment": "時代 (じだい): period, epoch, era, age, the times, those days, oldness, ancientness, antiquity, antique, period piece" },
		{ "question": "園女中時年", "answers": [ "中年女","ちゅうねんおんな" ], "comment": "中年女 (ちゅうねんおんな): middle-aged woman" },
		{ "question": "園実新人草", "answers": [ "新人","しんじん" ], "comment": "新人 (しんじん): new face, newcomer, rookie, fresh recruit, modern humans (from Cro-Magnon man onwards)" },
		{ "question": "園年徒前写", "answers": [ "前年","ぜんねん" ], "comment": "前年 (ぜんねん): the preceding year, the previous year, last year" },
		{ "question": "園気元番草", "answers": [ "元気","げんき" ], "comment": "元気 (げんき): lively, full of spirit, energetic, vigorous, vital, spirited, healthy, well, fit, in good health" },
		{ "question": "園水後内強", "answers": [ "園内","えんない" ], "comment": "園内 (えんない): inside the garden (park)" },
		{ "question": "園物人雨見", "answers": [ "見物人","けんぶつにん" ], "comment": "見物人 (けんぶつにん): spectator, sightseer, onlookers" },
		{ "question": "園理本気車", "answers": [ "本気","ほんき" ], "comment": "本気 (ほんき): seriousness, earnestness, truth, sanctity" },
		{ "question": "園花体強元", "answers": [ "花園","はなぞの","かえん" ], "comment": "花園 (はなぞの, かえん): flower garden, flower garden" },
		{ "question": "園草人前明", "answers": [ "人前","にんまえ","ひとまえ","前人","ぜんじん" ], "comment": "人前 (にんまえ, ひとまえ): portion of food, the public, company\n前人 (ぜんじん): predecessor, former people" },
		{ "question": "地写日牛番", "answers": [ "番地","ばんち","地番","ちばん" ], "comment": "番地 (ばんち): house number, address\n地番 (ちばん): lot number" },
		{ "question": "地徒給用王", "answers": [ "用地","ようち" ], "comment": "用地 (ようち): site" },
		{ "question": "地時女立科", "answers": [ "立地","りっち" ], "comment": "立地 (りっち): site, location (e.g. of industry)" },
		{ "question": "地空男王記", "answers": [ "空地","あきち","くうち" ], "comment": "空地 (あきち, くうち): vacant land, vacant land" },
		{ "question": "場中空交先", "answers": [ "空中","くうちゅう","中空","ちゅうくう","なかぞら" ], "comment": "空中 (くうちゅう): sky, air\n中空 (ちゅうくう, なかぞら): hollow, emptiness, mid-air, the air, hollow, emptiness, mid-air, the air" },
		{ "question": "場入車女命", "answers": [ "入場","にゅうじょう" ], "comment": "入場 (にゅうじょう): entrance, admission, entering" },
		{ "question": "場明心器文", "answers": [ "文明","ぶんめい","明文","めいぶん" ], "comment": "文明 (ぶんめい): civilization, civilisation, culture, Bummei era (1469.4.28-1487.7.20)\n明文 (めいぶん): explicit statement (e.g. law), express provision" },
		{ "question": "場生車番会", "answers": [ "会場","かいじょう" ], "comment": "会場 (かいじょう): assembly hall, meeting place, venue, grounds" },
		{ "question": "声前真見理", "answers": [ "真理","しんり" ], "comment": "真理 (しんり): truth" },
		{ "question": "声合夜中代", "answers": [ "夜中","よなか","やちゅう","よじゅう","中夜","ちゅうや" ], "comment": "夜中 (よなか, やちゅう, よじゅう): midnight, dead of night, during the night, at night, all night, the whole night\n中夜 (ちゅうや): midnight period, midnight service, winter solstice" },
		{ "question": "声術世手真", "answers": [ "手術","しゅじゅつ" ], "comment": "手術 (しゅじゅつ): (surgical) operation, procedure" },
		{ "question": "声記理花音", "answers": [ "音声","おんせい","おんじょう","声音","せいおん","こわね" ], "comment": "音声 (おんせい, おんじょう): voice, (the concept of) sound, voice, (the concept of) sound\n声音 (せいおん, こわね): vocal sound, tone of voice, vocal sound, tone of voice" },
		{ "question": "外文歩場男", "answers": [ "外場","がいば","場外","じょうがい" ], "comment": "外場 (がいば): external field\n場外 (じょうがい): outside the hall (or stadium, market, etc.), off the grounds, off the premises, off-track" },
		{ "question": "外真長給出", "answers": [ "外出","がいしゅつ","そとで" ], "comment": "外出 (がいしゅつ, そとで): outing, trip, going out, outing, trip, going out" },
		{ "question": "外配本徒進", "answers": [ "配本","はいほん" ], "comment": "配本 (はいほん): distribution of books" },
		{ "question": "夜体時生命", "answers": [ "生命体","せいめいたい" ], "comment": "生命体 (せいめいたい): life-form" },
		{ "question": "夜国作空火", "answers": [ "夜空","よぞら" ], "comment": "夜空 (よぞら): night sky" },
		{ "question": "夜大事火春", "answers": [ "大火事","おおかじ" ], "comment": "大火事 (おおかじ): big fire (buildings, etc. on fire)" },
		{ "question": "夜草月時芸", "answers": [ "月夜","つきよ" ], "comment": "月夜 (つきよ): moonlit night" },
		{ "question": "夜見入国牛", "answers": [ "入国","にゅうこく","にゅうごく" ], "comment": "入国 (にゅうこく, にゅうごく): entry to a country, entry to a country" },
		{ "question": "夜重中真念", "answers": [ "真夜中","まよなか" ], "comment": "真夜中 (まよなか): dead of night, midnight" },
		{ "question": "大作科歩春", "answers": [ "大作","たいさく" ], "comment": "大作 (たいさく): epic" },
		{ "question": "大徒配時代", "answers": [ "大時代","おおじだい","だいじだい" ], "comment": "大時代 (おおじだい, だいじだい): old-fashioned, antiquated, anachronistic, old-fashioned, antiquated, anachronistic" },
		{ "question": "大春国夜世", "answers": [ "国大","こくだい","大国","たいこく" ], "comment": "国大 (こくだい): national university\n大国 (たいこく): large country, major powers" },
		{ "question": "大楽写体世", "answers": [ "大体","だいたい" ], "comment": "大体 (だいたい): outline, main point, gist, general, substantially, approximately, about, in the first place, to begin with, from the start" },
		{ "question": "大物夜集元", "answers": [ "大物","おおもの" ], "comment": "大物 (おおもの): important person, big-shot, bigwig, big game (animal, fish), big thing, valuable thing" },
		{ "question": "大番草分給", "answers": [ "大分","だいぶ","だいぶん" ], "comment": "大分 (だいぶ, だいぶん): considerably, greatly, a lot, considerably, greatly, a lot" },
		{ "question": "大紙真後見", "answers": [ "後見","こうけん" ], "comment": "後見 (こうけん): guardianship, guardian, (theatrical) assistant, prompter" },
		{ "question": "大配肉事新", "answers": [ "事大","じだい","大事","だいじ","おおごと" ], "comment": "事大 (じだい): subserviency to the stronger\n大事 (だいじ, おおごと): important, valuable, serious matter, safe (Tochigi dialect), OK, important, valuable, serious matter, safe (Tochigi dialect), OK" },
		{ "question": "女場記内芸", "answers": [ "場内","じょうない" ], "comment": "場内 (じょうない): in-house, (on) the grounds, (in) the premises, hall, theatre, theater" },
		{ "question": "女文流術外", "answers": [ "女流","じょりゅう" ], "comment": "女流 (じょりゅう): woman (writer, artist, aviator, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "女文火面夜", "answers": [ "文面","ぶんめん" ], "comment": "文面 (ぶんめん): content of a letter" },
		{ "question": "女男格肉国", "answers": [ "男女","だんじょ","なんにょ","おとこおんな","女男","おんなおとこ" ], "comment": "男女 (だんじょ, なんにょ, おとこおんな): men and women, man and woman, both sexes, both genders, men and women, man and woman, both sexes, both genders, masculine woman, mannish woman, feminine man, effeminate man, intersexual, hermaphrodite\n女男 (おんなおとこ): feminine man, effeminate man, masculine woman, mannish woman" },
		{ "question": "学体月進念", "answers": [ "進学","しんがく" ], "comment": "進学 (しんがく): entering a higher-level school, esp. going on to university" },
		{ "question": "学園芸合白", "answers": [ "園芸学","えんげいがく" ], "comment": "園芸学 (えんげいがく): study of horticulture" },
		{ "question": "学強草配生", "answers": [ "学生","がくせい","がくしょう","がくそう" ], "comment": "学生 (がくせい, がくしょう, がくそう): student (esp. a university student), Heian-period student of government administration, Buddhist scholar, researcher at a Buddhist temple, person studying Buddhism, learning, scholarship, Heian-period student of government administration, Buddhist scholar, researcher at a Buddhist temple, person studying Buddhism, learning, scholarship" },
		{ "question": "学理元器車", "answers": [ "学理","がくり","理学","りがく" ], "comment": "学理 (がくり): scholarly principle, scientific principle\n理学 (りがく): physical science (e.g. chemistry, biology, etc.), physics, lixue (Song-era Chinese philosophy), philosophy" },
		{ "question": "学給明心理", "answers": [ "心理学","しんりがく" ], "comment": "心理学 (しんりがく): psychology" },
		{ "question": "学言楽色力", "answers": [ "学力","がくりょく","力学","りきがく" ], "comment": "学力 (がくりょく): scholarly ability, scholarship, knowledge, literary ability\n力学 (りきがく): mechanics, dynamics" },
		{ "question": "学記牛長春", "answers": [ "学長","がくちょう" ], "comment": "学長 (がくちょう): university president" },
		{ "question": "安日目新会", "answers": [ "目安","めやす","安目","やすめ" ], "comment": "目安 (めやす): criterion, standard, yardstick, reference, aim, rough estimate, approximation\n安目 (やすめ): on the cheap side, comparatively cheap" },
		{ "question": "安重春名人", "answers": [ "人名","じんめい","名人","めいじん" ], "comment": "人名 (じんめい): person's name\n名人 (めいじん): master, expert" },
		{ "question": "実内世音念", "answers": [ "内実","ないじつ" ], "comment": "内実 (ないじつ): the facts" },
		{ "question": "実格前芸気", "answers": [ "気前","きまえ" ], "comment": "気前 (きまえ): generosity" },
		{ "question": "年所牛学中", "answers": [ "中学年","ちゅうがくねん" ], "comment": "中学年 (ちゅうがくねん): middle grades of primary school (third and fourth grades)" },
		{ "question": "年明立風後", "answers": [ "明後年","みょうごねん" ], "comment": "明後年 (みょうごねん): year after next" },
		{ "question": "年時流道真", "answers": [ "時流","じりゅう" ], "comment": "時流 (じりゅう): fashion (current) of the times, general drift of affairs" },
		{ "question": "年格力白面", "answers": [ "面白","おもしろ","白面","はくめん","しらふ" ], "comment": "面白 (おもしろ): amusing, interesting\n白面 (はくめん, しらふ): fair complexion, face without makeup, inexperience, sobriety, soberness, sober face" },
		{ "question": "年配作花歩", "answers": [ "年配","ねんぱい" ], "comment": "年配 (ねんぱい): elderly, age, years" },
		{ "question": "強声出生見", "answers": [ "出生","しゅっしょう","しゅっせい" ], "comment": "出生 (しゅっしょう, しゅっせい): birth, birth" },
		{ "question": "強集春人名", "answers": [ "人名","じんめい","名人","めいじん" ], "comment": "人名 (じんめい): person's name\n名人 (めいじん): master, expert" },
		{ "question": "後交集大地", "answers": [ "大地","だいち" ], "comment": "大地 (だいち): ground, earth, the solid earth, the (vast) land" },
		{ "question": "後内和前草", "answers": [ "前後","ぜんご","まえしりえ" ], "comment": "前後 (ぜんご, まえしりえ): front and rear, front and back, before and behind, back and forth, before and after, order, context, consequences, inversion, reversion, getting out of order, co-occurring, around, about, approximately, nearly, front and rear, front and back, before and behind" },
		{ "question": "後水大内交", "answers": [ "大水","おおみず" ], "comment": "大水 (おおみず): flood" },
		{ "question": "後給園安物", "answers": [ "安物","やすもの" ], "comment": "安物 (やすもの): cheap article, poor quality article" },
		{ "question": "後色真芸半", "answers": [ "後半","こうはん" ], "comment": "後半 (こうはん): second half, latter half" },
		{ "question": "後草給立分", "answers": [ "分立","ぶんりつ" ], "comment": "分立 (ぶんりつ): segregation, separation, independence" },
		{ "question": "徒交立芸外", "answers": [ "外交","がいこう" ], "comment": "外交 (がいこう): diplomacy, selling (e.g. door-to-door), canvassing" },
		{ "question": "心中交格歩", "answers": [ "しんじゅう","しんぢゅう","ちゅうしん","心中","しんちゅう","中心","なかご" ], "comment": "心中 (しんじゅう, しんぢゅう): double suicide, lovers suicide, double suicide, lovers suicide\n中心 (ちゅうしん): center, centre, middle, heart, core, focus, pivot, emphasis, balance, -centered, -centred, -focussed, -oriented, centered on, focussed on\n心中 (しんちゅう): in one's heart, true motives, mind\n中心 (なかご): core, tang (of a sword, etc.), middle of a nest of boxes" },
		{ "question": "心人草入器", "answers": [ "人心","じんしん","ひとごころ" ], "comment": "人心 (じんしん, ひとごころ): human nature, human heart, human spirit, kindness, sympathy, human nature, human heart, human spirit, kindness, sympathy" },
		{ "question": "心年所月歩", "answers": [ "年月","としつき","ねんげつ" ], "comment": "年月 (としつき, ねんげつ): months and years, months and years" },
		{ "question": "心日場和行", "answers": [ "日和","ひより","びより" ], "comment": "日和 (ひより, びより): weather, climatic conditions, fine weather, clear day, situation, state of affairs, sea conditions, good day for sailing, ideal weather (for some action, event, etc.), perfect day" },
		{ "question": "心月理進紙", "answers": [ "心理","しんり" ], "comment": "心理 (しんり): state of mind, mentality, psychology" },
		{ "question": "心芸肉前空", "answers": [ "空前","くうぜん" ], "comment": "空前 (くうぜん): unprecedented, record-breaking" },
		{ "question": "心言出地半", "answers": [ "ここち","地心","ちしん","心地","しんじ" ], "comment": "心地 (ここち): feeling, sensation, mood, sensation of doing (usu. after -masu stem of verb)\n地心 (ちしん): center of the earth, centre of the earth\n心地 (しんじ): padding, lining, foundation" },
		{ "question": "心記文給入", "answers": [ "記入","きにゅう" ], "comment": "記入 (きにゅう): entry, filling in of forms" },
		{ "question": "心集作目内", "answers": [ "内心","ないしん" ], "comment": "内心 (ないしん): innermost thoughts, real intention, inmost heart, one's mind, in the heart, inner center (centre)" },
		{ "question": "念世色白器", "answers": [ "色白","いろじろ","白色","はくしょく" ], "comment": "色白 (いろじろ): fair-skinned, light-complexioned\n白色 (はくしょく): white" },
		{ "question": "念交後事新", "answers": [ "後事","こうじ","事後","じご" ], "comment": "後事 (こうじ): future affairs, affairs after one's death\n事後 (じご): after-, post-, ex-, after the fact, ex post" },
		{ "question": "念国気地意", "answers": [ "意気地","いくじ","いきじ" ], "comment": "意気地 (いくじ, いきじ): self-respect, self-confidence, guts, backbone, self-respect, self-confidence, guts, backbone" },
		{ "question": "念場格日中", "answers": [ "中日","ちゅうにち","なかび","日中","にっちゅう","ひなか" ], "comment": "中日 (ちゅうにち, なかび): China and Japan, the middle day, the equinoctial day, middle day (e.g sumo tournament, run of theatrical performances, etc.)\n日中 (にっちゅう, ひなか): daytime, during the day, Sino-Japanese, daytime, during the day, Sino-Japanese" },
		{ "question": "念夜国前所", "answers": [ "前夜","ぜんや","夜前","やぜん" ], "comment": "前夜 (ぜんや): last night, the previous night, night before (Christmas, etc.), eve (of festival, major event, etc.)\n夜前 (やぜん): last night" },
		{ "question": "念安入体番", "answers": [ "入念","にゅうねん" ], "comment": "入念 (にゅうねん): careful, elaborate, scrupulous" },
		{ "question": "念歩前分理", "answers": [ "理念","りねん" ], "comment": "理念 (りねん): (Platonic) ideal (of how things ought to be, e.g. human rights), foundational principle, idea, conception (e.g. of the university), doctrine, ideology" },
		{ "question": "念歩後中心", "answers": [ "しんじゅう","しんぢゅう","ちゅうしん","心中","しんちゅう","中心","なかご" ], "comment": "心中 (しんじゅう, しんぢゅう): double suicide, lovers suicide, double suicide, lovers suicide\n中心 (ちゅうしん): center, centre, middle, heart, core, focus, pivot, emphasis, balance, -centered, -centred, -focussed, -oriented, centered on, focussed on\n心中 (しんちゅう): in one's heart, true motives, mind\n中心 (なかご): core, tang (of a sword, etc.), middle of a nest of boxes" },
		{ "question": "念歩真記雨", "answers": [ "記念","きねん" ], "comment": "記念 (きねん): commemoration, celebration, honoring the memory of something, turning something into a memento, memory" },
		{ "question": "念間格夜足", "answers": [ "夜間","やかん" ], "comment": "夜間 (やかん): at night, nighttime" },
		{ "question": "念音新記日", "answers": [ "記念日","きねんび" ], "comment": "記念日 (きねんび): holiday, anniversary, memorial day" },
		{ "question": "意先交目徒", "answers": [ "目先","めさき" ], "comment": "目先 (めさき): near future, immediate, before one's eyes, under one's nose" },
		{ "question": "意数写園日", "answers": [ "数日","すうじつ","日数","にっすう","ひかず" ], "comment": "数日 (すうじつ): few days\n日数 (にっすう, ひかず): a number of days, a number of days" },
		{ "question": "意物食記車", "answers": [ "食物","しょくもつ","くいもの" ], "comment": "食物 (しょくもつ, くいもの): food, foodstuff, food, foodstuff, prey, victim" },
		{ "question": "意真番男学", "answers": [ "真意","しんい" ], "comment": "真意 (しんい): real intention, true motive, true meaning" },
		{ "question": "意記交命地", "answers": [ "意地","いじ" ], "comment": "意地 (いじ): stubbornness, obstinacy, willpower, pride, disposition, nature, appetite, desire, greed" },
		{ "question": "意進新足肉", "answers": [ "新進","しんしん" ], "comment": "新進 (しんしん): rising, up-and-coming" },
		{ "question": "所中力発命", "answers": [ "命中","めいちゅう" ], "comment": "命中 (めいちゅう): a hit, hitting something that was aimed at" },
		{ "question": "所交発給物", "answers": [ "発給","はっきゅう" ], "comment": "発給 (はっきゅう): issuance (e.g. of a passport), issuing" },
		{ "question": "所人半文交", "answers": [ "人文","じんぶん","じんもん","文人","ぶんじん","ふみびと" ], "comment": "人文 (じんぶん, じんもん): humanity, civilization, civilisation, culture, humanity, civilization, civilisation, culture\n文人 (ぶんじん, ふみびと): person of letters, literary person, person of letters, poet" },
		{ "question": "所春目体場", "answers": [ "春場所","はるばしょ" ], "comment": "春場所 (はるばしょ): spring (March) tournament, held in Osaka" },
		{ "question": "所物親器数", "answers": [ "器物","きぶつ","うつわもの" ], "comment": "器物 (きぶつ, うつわもの): container, receptacle, utensil, implement, furniture, calibre, talent, ability, personal property, container, receptacle, utensil, implement, furniture, calibre, talent, ability, personal property" },
		{ "question": "所身物学理", "answers": [ "物理学","ぶつりがく" ], "comment": "物理学 (ぶつりがく): physics" },
		{ "question": "手園作面王", "answers": [ "王手","おうて" ], "comment": "王手 (おうて): check" },
		{ "question": "手声学生物", "answers": [ "生物学","せいぶつがく" ], "comment": "生物学 (せいぶつがく): biology" },
		{ "question": "手大紙明時", "answers": [ "大手紙","おおてし" ], "comment": "大手紙 (おおてし): major newspapers" },
		{ "question": "手後白和春", "answers": [ "後手","ごて" ], "comment": "後手 (ごて): losing initiative, being forestalled, second move (in go or shogi), moving second, person with the second move, rear guard" },
		{ "question": "手新日念目", "answers": [ "新手","あらて","しんて" ], "comment": "新手 (あらて, しんて): fresh supply of troops, newcomer, new method, new trick, fresh supply of troops, newcomer, new method, new trick" },
		{ "question": "手気半食強", "answers": [ "強気","つよき","ごうぎ","ごうき" ], "comment": "強気 (つよき, ごうぎ, ごうき): confident, assured, self-assured, firm, strong, cocksure, bullish (e.g. market), great, grand, obstinate, stubborn, great, grand, obstinate, stubborn" },
		{ "question": "手空意園日", "answers": [ "空手","からて" ], "comment": "空手 (からて): karate, empty handed" },
		{ "question": "手道牛前親", "answers": [ "手前","てまえ","てめえ" ], "comment": "手前 (てまえ, てめえ): before, this side, one's standpoint, one's appearance, we, you, you (used by young males), oneself" },
		{ "question": "数学作給写", "answers": [ "数学","すうがく" ], "comment": "数学 (すうがく): mathematics, arithmetic" },
		{ "question": "数意雨流日", "answers": [ "数日","すうじつ","日数","にっすう","ひかず" ], "comment": "数日 (すうじつ): few days\n日数 (にっすう, ひかず): a number of days, a number of days" },
		{ "question": "数長徒実前", "answers": [ "実数","じっすう" ], "comment": "実数 (じっすう): real number" },
		{ "question": "数間後配時", "answers": [ "数時間","すうじかん" ], "comment": "数時間 (すうじかん): a few hours" },
		{ "question": "数風重長心", "answers": [ "重心","じゅうしん" ], "comment": "重心 (じゅうしん): centre of gravity (center), centroid, barycenter, (one's) balance" },
		{ "question": "文新立徒楽", "answers": [ "文楽","ぶんらく" ], "comment": "文楽 (ぶんらく): Japanese puppet theatre (theater), bunraku" },
		{ "question": "文本発女記", "answers": [ "本文","ほんぶん","ほんもん" ], "comment": "本文 (ほんぶん, ほんもん): text (of document), body (of letter), text (of document), body (of letter)" },
		{ "question": "文花合力世", "answers": [ "合力","ごうりょく","ごうりき","こうりょく" ], "comment": "合力 (ごうりょく, ごうりき, こうりょく): resultant force, assistance, help, donation, alms, almsgiving, resultant force, assistance, help, donation, alms, almsgiving, resultant force, assistance, help, donation, alms, almsgiving" },
		{ "question": "文芸進間給", "answers": [ "文芸","ぶんげい","芸文","げいぶん" ], "comment": "文芸 (ぶんげい): literature, art and literature, belles-lettres\n芸文 (げいぶん): art and literature" },
		{ "question": "文雨体出王", "answers": [ "文体","ぶんたい","体文","たいもん" ], "comment": "文体 (ぶんたい): literary style\n体文 (たいもん): consonant (in the Siddham script)" },
		{ "question": "新世物理国", "answers": [ "物理","ぶつり" ], "comment": "物理 (ぶつり): physics, law of nature" },
		{ "question": "新事番春器", "answers": [ "新春","しんしゅん" ], "comment": "新春 (しんしゅん): New Year (Spring)" },
		{ "question": "新元空本徒", "answers": [ "元本","がんぽん","げんぽん","本元","ほんもと" ], "comment": "元本 (がんぽん, げんぽん): principal (invest.), capital, principal (invest.), capital\n本元 (ほんもと): origin, main branch of family" },
		{ "question": "新出写園楽", "answers": [ "楽園","らくえん" ], "comment": "楽園 (らくえん): pleasure garden, paradise" },
		{ "question": "日前心牛流", "answers": [ "前日","ぜんじつ","まえび" ], "comment": "前日 (ぜんじつ, まえび): previous day, day before, eve, prior day, preceding day, previous day, day before, eve, prior day, preceding day" },
		{ "question": "日合明園徒", "answers": [ "明日","あした","あす","みょうにち" ], "comment": "明日 (あした, あす, みょうにち): tomorrow, near future, tomorrow, near future, tomorrow, near future" },
		{ "question": "日後紙園会", "answers": [ "後日","ごじつ","ごにち" ], "comment": "後日 (ごじつ, ごにち): in the future, another day, later, in the future, another day, later" },
		{ "question": "日念新親流", "answers": [ "親日","しんにち" ], "comment": "親日 (しんにち): pro-Japanese" },
		{ "question": "日格念番力", "answers": [ "念力","ねんりき" ], "comment": "念力 (ねんりき): will-power, faith, telekinesis, psychokinesis" },
		{ "question": "日牛念中紙", "answers": [ "中日","ちゅうにち","なかび","日中","にっちゅう","ひなか" ], "comment": "中日 (ちゅうにち, なかび): China and Japan, the middle day, the equinoctial day, middle day (e.g sumo tournament, run of theatrical performances, etc.)\n日中 (にっちゅう, ひなか): daytime, during the day, Sino-Japanese, daytime, during the day, Sino-Japanese" },
		{ "question": "日芸出集内", "answers": [ "日出","にっしゅつ" ], "comment": "日出 (にっしゅつ): sunrise" },
		{ "question": "明命発重間", "answers": [ "発明","はつめい" ], "comment": "発明 (はつめい): invention, intelligent, clever, being enlightened, having the meaning of everything become clear" },
		{ "question": "明後日合立", "answers": [ "明後日","あさって","みょうごにち" ], "comment": "明後日 (あさって, みょうごにち): day after tomorrow, day after tomorrow" },
		{ "question": "明手風本立", "answers": [ "手本","てほん","本手","ほんて" ], "comment": "手本 (てほん): copybook, model, pattern\n本手 (ほんて): one's true ability, the right way, professional" },
		{ "question": "明気数手出", "answers": [ "手数","てすう","てかず" ], "comment": "手数 (てすう, てかず): trouble, bother, number of moves (in go, shogi, etc.), number of punches (in boxing), trouble, bother, number of moves (in go, shogi, etc.), number of punches (in boxing)" },
		{ "question": "明花間科世", "answers": [ "世間","せけん" ], "comment": "世間 (せけん): world, society" },
		{ "question": "春園声紙大", "answers": [ "大声","おおごえ","たいせい" ], "comment": "大声 (おおごえ, たいせい): loud voice, loud voice" },
		{ "question": "春外時見火", "answers": [ "外見","がいけん","そとみ" ], "comment": "外見 (がいけん, そとみ): outward appearance, outward appearance" },
		{ "question": "春後白芸生", "answers": [ "後生","こうせい","ごしょう","生後","せいご" ], "comment": "後生 (こうせい, ごしょう): younger people, future generations, afterlife\n生後 (せいご): post-natal, since birth" },
		{ "question": "春科地言面", "answers": [ "地面","じめん" ], "comment": "地面 (じめん): ground, earth's surface" },
		{ "question": "春科身食会", "answers": [ "会食","かいしょく" ], "comment": "会食 (かいしょく): dining together, mess" },
		{ "question": "春草集年長", "answers": [ "長年","ながねん","年長","ねんちょう" ], "comment": "長年 (ながねん): long time, many years, long time, many years\n年長 (ねんちょう): seniority" },
		{ "question": "春行代安声", "answers": [ "代行","だいこう" ], "comment": "代行 (だいこう): acting as agent" },
		{ "question": "春足分歩草", "answers": [ "春分","しゅんぶん" ], "comment": "春分 (しゅんぶん): vernal equinox, spring equinox" },
		{ "question": "春足王世元", "answers": [ "足元","あしもと" ], "comment": "足元 (あしもと): at one's feet, underfoot, one's step (as in \"watch your step\"), gait, pace, step, most recent, current, you, thou, at one's feet, underfoot, one's step (as in \"watch your step\"), gait, pace, step, most recent, current, you, thou" },
		{ "question": "時体記国集", "answers": [ "国体","こくたい" ], "comment": "国体 (こくたい): national polity, National Athletic Meet" },
		{ "question": "時地親芸力", "answers": [ "地力","ちりょく","じりき" ], "comment": "地力 (ちりょく, じりき): fertility, one's own potential, real ability, one's own strength" },
		{ "question": "時実行集立", "answers": [ "実行時","じっこうじ" ], "comment": "実行時 (じっこうじ): execution-time, run time, object time" },
		{ "question": "時心肉園会", "answers": [ "会心","かいしん" ], "comment": "会心 (かいしん): congeniality, satisfaction" },
		{ "question": "時番紙年日", "answers": [ "日時","にちじ","時日","じじつ" ], "comment": "日時 (にちじ): date and time\n時日 (じじつ): date, time" },
		{ "question": "時草和半真", "answers": [ "半時","はんとき","はんじ","時半","じはん" ], "comment": "半時 (はんとき, はんじ): little while, short time, an hour, half-hour, half an hour, little while, short time, an hour, half-hour, half an hour\n時半 (じはん): about an hour, short time, half past (the hour)" },
		{ "question": "時草和大念", "answers": [ "大和","やまと" ], "comment": "大和 (やまと): Yamato, ancient province corresponding to modern-day Nara Prefecture, (ancient) Japan, Japanese" },
		{ "question": "時見念物重", "answers": [ "見物","けんぶつ","みもの","物見","ものみ" ], "comment": "見物 (けんぶつ, みもの): sightseeing, watching, viewing, sightseer, watcher, spectator, sight, attraction, spectacle, something worth seeing\n物見 (ものみ): sightseeing, scout, patrol, watchtower, lookout" },
		{ "question": "時身科所中", "answers": [ "中身","なかみ","身中","しんちゅう" ], "comment": "中身 (なかみ): contents, interior, substance, filling, (sword) blade\n身中 (しんちゅう): within one's body" },
		{ "question": "時雨外芸火", "answers": [ "時雨","しぐれ","じう" ], "comment": "時雨 (しぐれ, じう): drizzle, shower in late autumn (fall) or early winter, seasonable rain, drizzle, shower in late autumn (fall) or early winter, seasonable rain" },
		{ "question": "月半合器心", "answers": [ "半月","はんつき","はんげつ" ], "comment": "半月 (はんつき, はんげつ): half-moon, half month, semicircle, half-moon, half month, semicircle" },
		{ "question": "月年流心日", "answers": [ "年月日","ねんがっぴ" ], "comment": "年月日 (ねんがっぴ): date" },
		{ "question": "月日場実王", "answers": [ "月日","つきひ","がっぴ","日月","じつげつ","にちげつ" ], "comment": "月日 (つきひ, がっぴ): time, years, days, (the) date\n日月 (じつげつ, にちげつ): sun and moon, time, days, years, sun and moon, time, days, years" },
		{ "question": "月日意年紙", "answers": [ "年月日","ねんがっぴ" ], "comment": "年月日 (ねんがっぴ): date" },
		{ "question": "月生声年日", "answers": [ "生年月日","せいねんがっぴ" ], "comment": "生年月日 (せいねんがっぴ): birth date, date of birth, DOB" },
		{ "question": "月面所念合", "answers": [ "月面","げつめん" ], "comment": "月面 (げつめん): moon's surface" },
		{ "question": "本声数集事", "answers": [ "本数","ほんすう" ], "comment": "本数 (ほんすう): number of long thin objects (movies, TV programs, baseball games, etc.) (programmes)" },
		{ "question": "本流徒進牛", "answers": [ "本流","ほんりゅう" ], "comment": "本流 (ほんりゅう): main current, main current of thought" },
		{ "question": "本理記国行", "answers": [ "本国","ほんごく","国本","こくほん" ], "comment": "本国 (ほんごく): one's own country\n国本 (こくほん): foundation of the nation" },
		{ "question": "本紙夜実重", "answers": [ "本紙","ほんし" ], "comment": "本紙 (ほんし): this newspaper" },
		{ "question": "本雨理出所", "answers": [ "出所","しゅっしょ","でどころ","でどこ","所出","しょしゅつ" ], "comment": "出所 (しゅっしょ, でどころ, でどこ): origin, source, authority, birthplace, release (discharge) from prison, exit, point of departure, time to take action, origin, source, authority, birthplace, release (discharge) from prison, exit, point of departure, time to take action, origin, source, authority, birthplace, release (discharge) from prison, exit, point of departure, time to take action\n所出 (しょしゅつ): one's birthplace, source" },
		{ "question": "格世長安意", "answers": [ "格安","かくやす" ], "comment": "格安 (かくやす): cheap, reasonable" },
		{ "question": "格科立学流", "answers": [ "科学","かがく","学科","がっか" ], "comment": "科学 (かがく): science\n学科 (がっか): study subject, course of study, department (university, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "格集力先重", "answers": [ "重力","じゅうりょく" ], "comment": "重力 (じゅうりょく): gravity, gravitation, gravitational pull" },
		{ "question": "楽火間体生", "answers": [ "生体","せいたい" ], "comment": "生体 (せいたい): organism, living body" },
		{ "question": "歩中和念給", "answers": [ "中和","ちゅうわ" ], "comment": "中和 (ちゅうわ): neutralizing, neutralising, counteracting, neutral, unbiased" },
		{ "question": "歩力言実長", "answers": [ "実力","じつりょく" ], "comment": "実力 (じつりょく): (real) ability, true strength, merit, efficiency, competency, arms, force" },
		{ "question": "歩命生器力", "answers": [ "生命力","せいめいりょく" ], "comment": "生命力 (せいめいりょく): vitality, (one's) life force" },
		{ "question": "歩見進器面", "answers": [ "進歩","しんぽ" ], "comment": "進歩 (しんぽ): progress, advance, improvement, development" },
		{ "question": "歩身実徒水", "answers": [ "徒歩","とほ","かち" ], "comment": "徒歩 (とほ, かち): walking, going on foot, foot soldier (Edo period), samurai on foot, going on foot, walking" },
		{ "question": "歩長明生本", "answers": [ "生長","せいちょう","長生","ちょうせい" ], "comment": "生長 (せいちょう): growth, increment\n長生 (ちょうせい): longevity" },
		{ "question": "歩間念音食", "answers": [ "間食","かんしょく","食間","しょっかん" ], "comment": "間食 (かんしょく): eating between meals, snacking\n食間 (しょっかん): between meals" },
		{ "question": "気写色術半", "answers": [ "気色","きしょく","けしき","色気","いろけ" ], "comment": "気色 (きしょく, けしき): mood, humor, humour, looks, countenance, sign, indication\n色気 (いろけ): colouring, coloring, shade of colour, shade of color, sex appeal (esp. women), interest in the opposite sex, sensuality, seductiveness, glamor, glamour, sexual passion, romance, poetry, charm, desire, interest, inclination, ambition" },
		{ "question": "気徒楽白写", "answers": [ "気楽","きらく" ], "comment": "気楽 (きらく): carefree, comfortable, at ease, easygoing, happy-go-lucky" },
		{ "question": "気生親芸意", "answers": [ "生意気","なまいき" ], "comment": "生意気 (なまいき): impertinent, saucy, cheeky, conceit, audacious, brazen, feisty" },
		{ "question": "気空草牛出", "answers": [ "空気","くうき" ], "comment": "空気 (くうき): air, atmosphere, mood, situation, someone with no presence, someone who doesn't stand out at all" },
		{ "question": "気花足交意", "answers": [ "意気","いき" ], "comment": "意気 (いき): spirit, heart, disposition" },
		{ "question": "気芸力食王", "answers": [ "気力","きりょく" ], "comment": "気力 (きりょく): willpower, energy, vitality" },
		{ "question": "気足内記世", "answers": [ "内気","うちき" ], "comment": "内気 (うちき): bashfulness, shyness, reserve, timidity" },
		{ "question": "水立格力長", "answers": [ "水力","すいりょく","力水","ちからみず" ], "comment": "水力 (すいりょく): hydraulic power, water power\n力水 (ちからみず): water offered to wrestlers just prior to a bout" },
		{ "question": "流手科肉食", "answers": [ "食肉","しょくにく","肉食","にくしょく" ], "comment": "食肉 (しょくにく): meat (for consumption)\n肉食 (にくしょく): meat eating, eating of meat, meat diet, carnivorous" },
		{ "question": "流歩和紙事", "answers": [ "和紙","わし" ], "comment": "和紙 (わし): washi, Japanese paper" },
		{ "question": "流牛日進元", "answers": [ "元日","がんじつ","がんにち" ], "comment": "元日 (がんじつ, がんにち): New Year's Day, New Year's Day" },
		{ "question": "流王間安心", "answers": [ "安心","あんしん","あんじん" ], "comment": "安心 (あんしん, あんじん): relief, peace of mind, obtaining peace of mind through faith or ascetic practice" },
		{ "question": "火国発夜芸", "answers": [ "発火","はっか" ], "comment": "発火 (はっか): ignition, catching fire, firing (e.g. gun), discharging" },
		{ "question": "火番真空分", "answers": [ "真空","しんくう" ], "comment": "真空 (しんくう): vacuum, hollow, empty" },
		{ "question": "火間年身写", "answers": [ "年間","ねんかん" ], "comment": "年間 (ねんかん): years (period of)" },
		{ "question": "牛出用発記", "answers": [ "出発","しゅっぱつ","発出","はっしゅつ" ], "comment": "出発 (しゅっぱつ): departure\n発出 (はっしゅつ): issue, sending out" },
		{ "question": "牛半面空心", "answers": [ "半面","はんめん" ], "comment": "半面 (はんめん): half the face, one side, half, the other side, the reverse, the contrary" },
		{ "question": "牛命言人実", "answers": [ "人命","じんめい" ], "comment": "人命 (じんめい): (human) life" },
		{ "question": "牛女火音本", "answers": [ "本音","ほんね" ], "comment": "本音 (ほんね): real intention, motive, true opinion, what one really thinks" },
		{ "question": "牛新命花年", "answers": [ "新年","しんねん" ], "comment": "新年 (しんねん): New Year" },
		{ "question": "牛発作集日", "answers": [ "発作","ほっさ" ], "comment": "発作 (ほっさ): fit, spasm, attack, seizure" },
		{ "question": "牛芸本用年", "answers": [ "本年","ほんねん" ], "comment": "本年 (ほんねん): this (current) year" },
		{ "question": "牛行進術音", "answers": [ "行進","こうしん","進行","しんこう" ], "comment": "行進 (こうしん): march, parade\n進行 (しんこう): moving forward (e.g. vehicle), onward movement, advance (work, procedure, etc), advancement, progress, progress (of a disease), disease progression, progression (harmonic, melodic)" },
		{ "question": "牛見記地時", "answers": [ "見地","けんち" ], "comment": "見地 (けんち): point of view" },
		{ "question": "牛身念和交", "answers": [ "和牛","わぎゅう" ], "comment": "和牛 (わぎゅう): Wagyu beef, Japanese beef" },
		{ "question": "牛間新元体", "answers": [ "新体","しんたい" ], "comment": "新体 (しんたい): new style" },
		{ "question": "物写紙用世", "answers": [ "用紙","ようし" ], "comment": "用紙 (ようし): blank form, sheets of paper, sheet of paper" },
		{ "question": "物名術足給", "answers": [ "名物","めいぶつ" ], "comment": "名物 (めいぶつ): famous product, special product, speciality, specialty" },
		{ "question": "物学時格会", "answers": [ "学会","がっかい" ], "comment": "学会 (がっかい): scientific society, academic meeting, academic conference" },
		{ "question": "物牛人場重", "answers": [ "人物","じんぶつ" ], "comment": "人物 (じんぶつ): person, character, figure, personage, man, woman, one's character, one's personality, able person, talented person" },
		{ "question": "物空親牛本", "answers": [ "本物","ほんもの" ], "comment": "本物 (ほんもの): genuine article, real thing, real deal" },
		{ "question": "物身意道分", "answers": [ "身分","みぶん","分身","ぶんしん" ], "comment": "身分 (みぶん): social position, social status\n分身 (ぶんしん): parturition, delivery, one's child, branch, offshoot, one's other self" },
		{ "question": "王代人写給", "answers": [ "代人","だいにん" ], "comment": "代人 (だいにん): substitute, deputy, proxy, representative, agent" },
		{ "question": "王夜言理日", "answers": [ "日夜","にちや" ], "comment": "日夜 (にちや): day and night, always" },
		{ "question": "王年歩会気", "answers": [ "年会","ねんかい" ], "comment": "年会 (ねんかい): conference, annual convention" },
		{ "question": "王強番行元", "answers": [ "強行","きょうこう" ], "comment": "強行 (きょうこう): forcing, enforcement, forced, enforced" },
		{ "question": "王立術夜作", "answers": [ "王立","おうりつ" ], "comment": "王立 (おうりつ): royal" },
		{ "question": "王見学肉身", "answers": [ "見学","けんがく" ], "comment": "見学 (けんがく): inspection, study by observation, field trip" },
		{ "question": "王面本園日", "answers": [ "本日","ほんじつ","日本","にほん","にっぽん" ], "comment": "本日 (ほんじつ): today\n日本 (にほん, にっぽん): Japan, Japan" },
		{ "question": "理交立声事", "answers": [ "事理","じり","理事","りじ" ], "comment": "事理 (じり): reason, facts, propriety, sense\n理事 (りじ): director, board of directors" },
		{ "question": "理作日給花", "answers": [ "日給","にっきゅう" ], "comment": "日給 (にっきゅう): daily wages" },
		{ "question": "理合車時長", "answers": [ "合理","ごうり" ], "comment": "合理 (ごうり): rational" },
		{ "question": "理器場流中", "answers": [ "中流","ちゅうりゅう" ], "comment": "中流 (ちゅうりゅう): mid-stream, middle course, middle class" },
		{ "question": "理後白内進", "answers": [ "後進","こうしん" ], "comment": "後進 (こうしん): one's junior, next generation, reversing, going astern, going backwards" },
		{ "question": "理手配牛用", "answers": [ "手配","てはい" ], "comment": "手配 (てはい): arrangement, preparations, search (by police)" },
		{ "question": "理日牛立半", "answers": [ "半日","はんにち","はんじつ" ], "comment": "半日 (はんにち, はんじつ): half day, half day" },
		{ "question": "理春肉国名", "answers": [ "国名","こくめい" ], "comment": "国名 (こくめい): country name" },
		{ "question": "理重雨行先", "answers": [ "行先","いきさき","ゆきさき","先行","せんこう" ], "comment": "行先 (いきさき, ゆきさき): destination, whereabouts, address, destination, whereabouts, address\n先行 (せんこう): preceding, going first, leading, going ahead, taking priority" },
		{ "question": "生前牛格火", "answers": [ "生前","せいぜん","前生","ぜんしょう" ], "comment": "生前 (せいぜん): while alive, during one's lifetime\n前生 (ぜんしょう): previous existence" },
		{ "question": "生大学元春", "answers": [ "大学生","だいがくせい" ], "comment": "大学生 (だいがくせい): university student, college student" },
		{ "question": "生理給安番", "answers": [ "生理","せいり" ], "comment": "生理 (せいり): physiology, menstruation, one's period, menses" },
		{ "question": "生目強術発", "answers": [ "発生","はっせい" ], "comment": "発生 (はっせい): outbreak, spring forth, occurrence, incidence, generation (e.g. of power or heat), genesis, origin, ontogeny, development of complex multicellular structures from cell(s) in a simple state" },
		{ "question": "生給先心草", "answers": [ "先生","せんせい","せんじょう","シーサン" ], "comment": "先生 (せんせい, せんじょう, シーサン): teacher, master, doctor, with names of teachers, etc. as an honorific, previous existence, teacher, master, doctor, with names of teachers, etc. as an honorific, previous existence, boy" },
		{ "question": "用場意花学", "answers": [ "用意","ようい" ], "comment": "用意 (ようい): preparation, arrangements, provision, getting ready, laying out (e.g. a meal)" },
		{ "question": "用声車本中", "answers": [ "車中","しゃちゅう" ], "comment": "車中 (しゃちゅう): in a train or vehicle" },
		{ "question": "用歩心長新", "answers": [ "用心","ようじん" ], "comment": "用心 (ようじん): care, precaution, guarding, caution" },
		{ "question": "用記世科手", "answers": [ "手記","しゅき" ], "comment": "手記 (しゅき): note, memorandum" },
		{ "question": "男学人文科", "answers": [ "人文科学","じんぶんかがく" ], "comment": "人文科学 (じんぶんかがく): humanities, social sciences, liberal arts" },
		{ "question": "男新芸国力", "answers": [ "国力","こくりょく" ], "comment": "国力 (こくりょく): national power" },
		{ "question": "男足外配音", "answers": [ "足音","あしおと" ], "comment": "足音 (あしおと): footsteps (sound)" },
		{ "question": "男集術長草", "answers": [ "長男","ちょうなん" ], "comment": "長男 (ちょうなん): eldest son (may be the only son), first-born son" },
		{ "question": "番実配雨用", "answers": [ "実用","じつよう" ], "comment": "実用 (じつよう): practical use, utility" },
		{ "question": "番道大給集", "answers": [ "大道","だいどう","たいどう" ], "comment": "大道 (だいどう, たいどう): main street, avenue, main street, avenue" },
		{ "question": "発手番真半", "answers": [ "番手","ばんて","手番","てつがい" ], "comment": "番手 (ばんて): (yarn) count, n-th place (e.g. in a race), n-th in position (e.g. a starting lineup)\n手番 (てつがい): plan, arrangements" },
		{ "question": "発日雨食牛", "answers": [ "日食","にっしょく" ], "comment": "日食 (にっしょく): solar eclipse" },
		{ "question": "発時立国歩", "answers": [ "国立","こくりつ","立国","りっこく" ], "comment": "国立 (こくりつ): national\n立国 (りっこく): founding of a nation" },
		{ "question": "発本日集国", "answers": [ "日本国","にほんこく" ], "comment": "日本国 (にほんこく): Japan" },
		{ "question": "発楽配言科", "answers": [ "発言","はつげん" ], "comment": "発言 (はつげん): statement, remark, observation, utterance, speech, proposal" },
		{ "question": "発男元事記", "answers": [ "記事","きじ" ], "comment": "記事 (きじ): article, news story, report, account" },
		{ "question": "発番器入力", "answers": [ "入力","にゅうりょく" ], "comment": "入力 (にゅうりょく): input, (data) entry" },
		{ "question": "発立親本格", "answers": [ "本格","ほんかく" ], "comment": "本格 (ほんかく): original method or procedure, serious, orthodox, classical, genuine" },
		{ "question": "発草分術配", "answers": [ "配分","はいぶん","分配","ぶんぱい" ], "comment": "配分 (はいぶん): distribution, allotment\n分配 (ぶんぱい): division, splitting, sharing, distribution, dissemination, allocation" },
		{ "question": "発音牛前用", "answers": [ "発音","はつおん" ], "comment": "発音 (はつおん): pronunciation" },
		{ "question": "白事集春食", "answers": [ "食事","しょくじ" ], "comment": "食事 (しょくじ): meal, to eat" },
		{ "question": "白園風流番", "answers": [ "風流","ふうりゅう" ], "comment": "風流 (ふうりゅう): elegance, taste, refinement" },
		{ "question": "白学女徒所", "answers": [ "学徒","がくと" ], "comment": "学徒 (がくと): student, follower, students and pupils" },
		{ "question": "白本体器牛", "answers": [ "本体","ほんたい","ほんだい" ], "comment": "本体 (ほんたい, ほんだい): substance, real form, main part, main unit, body (of a machine), this machine, this appliance, object of worship (at a shrine, temple, etc.), noumenon, base price, pre-tax price, substance, real form, main part, main unit, body (of a machine), this machine, this appliance, object of worship (at a shrine, temple, etc.), noumenon, base price, pre-tax price" },
		{ "question": "白歩用学流", "answers": [ "流用","りゅうよう" ], "comment": "流用 (りゅうよう): diversion, appropriation (e.g. of funds), misappropriation, re-use (e.g. old computer parts), recycling" },
		{ "question": "白流実国外", "answers": [ "外国","がいこく","そとぐに","国外","こくがい" ], "comment": "外国 (がいこく, そとぐに): foreign country, foreign country\n国外 (こくがい): outside the country" },
		{ "question": "白親学分行", "answers": [ "親分","おやぶん" ], "comment": "親分 (おやぶん): boss, kingpin, chief, head (e.g. of a crime syndicate)" },
		{ "question": "白長世所火", "answers": [ "所長","しょちょう","長所","ちょうしょ" ], "comment": "所長 (しょちょう): chief, head (of an office, of a laboratory)\n長所 (ちょうしょ): strong point, merit, virtue, advantage" },
		{ "question": "目人言花親", "answers": [ "人目","ひとめ","じんもく" ], "comment": "人目 (ひとめ, じんもく): public gaze, public notice, public gaze, public notice" },
		{ "question": "目外会気念", "answers": [ "外気","がいき" ], "comment": "外気 (がいき): open air" },
		{ "question": "目肉世道番", "answers": [ "番目","ばんめ" ], "comment": "番目 (ばんめ): indicates position in a sequence, divisions of a kabuki performance" },
		{ "question": "真数新食後", "answers": [ "食後","しょくご" ], "comment": "食後 (しょくご): after a meal" },
		{ "question": "真足集写紙", "answers": [ "写真集","しゃしんしゅう" ], "comment": "写真集 (しゃしんしゅう): collection of photographs, photoalbum" },
		{ "question": "真長合進格", "answers": [ "合格","ごうかく" ], "comment": "合格 (ごうかく): success, passing (e.g. exam), eligibility" },
		{ "question": "真間徒月和", "answers": [ "月間","げっかん" ], "comment": "月間 (げっかん): month-long period, (during) month" },
		{ "question": "真音年王楽", "answers": [ "音楽","おんがく","楽音","がくおん" ], "comment": "音楽 (おんがく): music, musical movement\n楽音 (がくおん): musical note" },
		{ "question": "真食発見重", "answers": [ "発見","はっけん" ], "comment": "発見 (はっけん): discovery, detection, finding" },
		{ "question": "科月徒理身", "answers": [ "理科","りか" ], "comment": "理科 (りか): science" },
		{ "question": "科気心器先", "answers": [ "気心","きごころ","心気","しんき" ], "comment": "気心 (きごころ): temper, disposition\n心気 (しんき): mentality, mood, sentiment, feelings, fretfulness, tedium" },
		{ "question": "科用水園年", "answers": [ "用水","ようすい" ], "comment": "用水 (ようすい): irrigation water, water for fire, city water, cistern water" },
		{ "question": "科発念声花", "answers": [ "発声","はっせい" ], "comment": "発声 (はっせい): utterance, speaking, vocalization, vocalisation, enunciation, pronouncing, leading a group of people (in cheering, singing, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "科給入手言", "answers": [ "入手","にゅうしゅ" ], "comment": "入手 (にゅうしゅ): acquisition, obtaining, coming to hand" },
		{ "question": "科食進男年", "answers": [ "年男","としおとこ" ], "comment": "年男 (としおとこ): Man of the Year, referring to a man born in a year with the same Chinese zodiac sign as the current year" },
		{ "question": "空園格強体", "answers": [ "体格","たいかく" ], "comment": "体格 (たいかく): physique, constitution" },
		{ "question": "空外作会新", "answers": [ "新作","しんさく" ], "comment": "新作 (しんさく): new work, new production" },
		{ "question": "空後徒意世", "answers": [ "後世","こうせい","ごせ" ], "comment": "後世 (こうせい, ごせ): posterity, future life, life to come, the next world, afterlife, life after death" },
		{ "question": "空進念白春", "answers": [ "空白","くうはく" ], "comment": "空白 (くうはく): blank space, vacuum, space, null (NUL)" },
		{ "question": "立代交所音", "answers": [ "交代","こうたい" ], "comment": "交代 (こうたい): alternation, change, relief, relay, shift, substitution (sports, etc.), taking turns" },
		{ "question": "立心物歩元", "answers": [ "物心","ものごころ","ぶっしん" ], "comment": "物心 (ものごころ, ぶっしん): awareness of things around one, ability to understand what is going on around oneself, judgment, judgement, discretion, matter and mind" },
		{ "question": "立楽術念場", "answers": [ "立場","たちば" ], "comment": "立場 (たちば): standpoint, position, situation" },
		{ "question": "立道集人元", "answers": [ "人道","じんどう","にんどう" ], "comment": "人道 (じんどう, にんどう): humanity, sidewalk, footpath, human realm, humanity, sidewalk, footpath, human realm" },
		{ "question": "立雨花道文", "answers": [ "花道","はなみち","かどう" ], "comment": "花道 (はなみち, かどう): passage through audience to stage, flower arrangement" },
		{ "question": "紙人中実国", "answers": [ "中国人","ちゅうごくじん" ], "comment": "中国人 (ちゅうごくじん): Chinese person" },
		{ "question": "紙水道体集", "answers": [ "水道","すいどう" ], "comment": "水道 (すいどう): water service, water supply" },
		{ "question": "紙足色安作", "answers": [ "色紙","いろがみ","しきし" ], "comment": "色紙 (いろがみ, しきし): coloured paper, colored paper, square fancy cardboard, used for autographs, poetry, etc." },
		{ "question": "給人所意間", "answers": [ "人間","にんげん","じんかん" ], "comment": "人間 (にんげん, じんかん): human being, person, man, mankind, humankind, character (of a person), the world" },
		{ "question": "給分強人白", "answers": [ "白人","はくじん" ], "comment": "白人 (はくじん): white person, Caucasian" },
		{ "question": "給夜火出意", "answers": [ "出火","しゅっか" ], "comment": "出火 (しゅっか): outbreak of fire" },
		{ "question": "給春安地実", "answers": [ "実地","じっち" ], "comment": "実地 (じっち): practice, the actual site" },
		{ "question": "給格術実水", "answers": [ "給水","きゅうすい" ], "comment": "給水 (きゅうすい): water supply" },
		{ "question": "給芸面代外", "answers": [ "外面","がいめん","そとづら","げめん" ], "comment": "外面 (がいめん, そとづら, げめん): outer surface, outward appearance, outside, exterior, outside, outer, outward, exterior, external, outer surface, outward appearance, outside, exterior, outside, outer, outward, exterior, external, outer surface, outward appearance, outside, exterior, outside, outer, outward, exterior, external" },
		{ "question": "給草理中人", "answers": [ "ひとなか","ちゅうにん","ちゅうじん","人中","じんちゅう","にんちゅう","中人","なかびと","なかひと" ], "comment": "人中 (ひとなか): society, company, the public, the world\n中人 (ちゅうにん, ちゅうじん): child in elementary or middle school, go-between, intermediary, middleman, mediator, intercessor, person of middling talent, strength, etc., middle-class person, bourgeois person, child in elementary or middle school, go-between, intermediary, middleman, mediator, intercessor, person of middling talent, strength, etc., middle-class person, bourgeois person\n人中 (じんちゅう, にんちゅう): in company, among people, philtrum, groove in the upper lip that runs from the bottom of the nose to the lip, in company, among people, philtrum, groove in the upper lip that runs from the bottom of the nose to the lip\n中人 (なかびと, なかひと): go-between, matchmaker, go-between, matchmaker, go-between, matchmaker" },
		{ "question": "給間用歩事", "answers": [ "用事","ようじ" ], "comment": "用事 (ようじ): tasks, things to do, errand, business (to take care of), affairs, engagement" },
		{ "question": "肉地行元世", "answers": [ "地元","じもと" ], "comment": "地元 (じもと): home area, home town, local" },
		{ "question": "肉大場術面", "answers": [ "場面","ばめん" ], "comment": "場面 (ばめん): scene, setting (e.g. of novel)" },
		{ "question": "肉徒数年国", "answers": [ "数年","すうねん","年数","ねんすう" ], "comment": "数年 (すうねん): several years\n年数 (ねんすう): number of years" },
		{ "question": "肉花分用気", "answers": [ "気分","きぶん" ], "comment": "気分 (きぶん): feeling, mood" },
		{ "question": "肉言場和道", "answers": [ "道場","どうじょう" ], "comment": "道場 (どうじょう): dojo (hall used for martial arts training), manda (place of Buddhist practice or meditation, esp. the place under the bodhi tree where Buddha attained enlightenment)" },
		{ "question": "色所強器風", "answers": [ "強風","きょうふう" ], "comment": "強風 (きょうふう): strong wind, high wind, moderate gale" },
		{ "question": "色立集車音", "answers": [ "音色","ねいろ","おんしょく" ], "comment": "音色 (ねいろ, おんしょく): tone color, tone colour, tone quality, timbre, synthesizer patch, synthesiser patch, tone color, tone colour, tone quality, timbre, synthesizer patch, synthesiser patch" },
		{ "question": "花外数意給", "answers": [ "意外","いがい" ], "comment": "意外 (いがい): unexpected, surprising" },
		{ "question": "花本命進芸", "answers": [ "本命","ほんめい" ], "comment": "本命 (ほんめい): favorite, favourite, sure thing, likely winner, certainty, one's heart's desire" },
		{ "question": "花歩立男生", "answers": [ "生花","いけばな","せいか" ], "comment": "生花 (いけばな, せいか): flower arrangement, fresh flowers, flower arrangement, fresh flowers" },
		{ "question": "花流火文数", "answers": [ "火花","ひばな","花火","はなび" ], "comment": "火花 (ひばな): spark\n花火 (はなび): fireworks" },
		{ "question": "花白後数火", "answers": [ "火花","ひばな","花火","はなび" ], "comment": "火花 (ひばな): spark\n花火 (はなび): fireworks" },
		{ "question": "芸会白合親", "answers": [ "会合","かいごう" ], "comment": "会合 (かいごう): meeting, assembly, association, conjunction" },
		{ "question": "芸入外牛科", "answers": [ "外科","げか" ], "comment": "外科 (げか): surgery, department of surgery (hospital, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "草入年白長", "answers": [ "長年","ながねん","年長","ねんちょう" ], "comment": "長年 (ながねん): long time, many years, long time, many years\n年長 (ねんちょう): seniority" },
		{ "question": "草合足学夜", "answers": [ "夜学","やがく" ], "comment": "夜学 (やがく): evening course, night-school" },
		{ "question": "草月力器給", "answers": [ "月給","げっきゅう" ], "comment": "月給 (げっきゅう): monthly salary" },
		{ "question": "草月名理牛", "answers": [ "名月","めいげつ" ], "comment": "名月 (めいげつ): harvest moon, bright moon, full moon" },
		{ "question": "草白数花牛", "answers": [ "草花","くさばな","そうか" ], "comment": "草花 (くさばな, そうか): flower, flowering plant, flower, flowering plant" },
		{ "question": "草親国中重", "answers": [ "国中","くにじゅう","こくじゅう","こくちゅう","中国","ちゅうごく" ], "comment": "国中 (くにじゅう, こくじゅう, こくちゅう): all over the country, all over the country, all over the country\n中国 (ちゅうごく): China, Chugoku region of western Honshu (incl. Okayama, Hiroshima, Shimane, Tottori and Yamaguchi prefectures), central part of a country, main region" },
		{ "question": "草面心代先", "answers": [ "先代","せんだい" ], "comment": "先代 (せんだい): family predecessor, previous age, previous generation" },
		{ "question": "草食半見集", "answers": [ "草食","そうしょく","食草","しょくそう" ], "comment": "草食 (そうしょく): herbivorous, plant-eating, graminivorous\n食草 (しょくそう): edible grass (for insects), larval food plant" },
		{ "question": "行世面目男", "answers": [ "面目","めんぼく","めんもく","めいぼく","目面","めづら","めつら" ], "comment": "面目 (めんぼく, めんもく, めいぼく): face, honour, honor, reputation, prestige, dignity, credit, appearance, look, face, honour, honor, reputation, prestige, dignity, credit, appearance, look, face, honour, honor, reputation, prestige, dignity, credit, appearance, look\n目面 (めづら, めつら): face and eyes, look, expression, features, face and eyes, look, expression, features" },
		{ "question": "行元春発外", "answers": [ "発行","はっこう" ], "comment": "発行 (はっこう): issue (publications), publishing, raising an event (software)" },
		{ "question": "行心肉集外", "answers": [ "心外","しんがい","外心","がいしん" ], "comment": "心外 (しんがい): regrettable, vexing, upsetting, unthinkable, wholly unexpected\n外心 (がいしん): circumcenter, circumcentre, outer center, outer centre" },
		{ "question": "行念風事声", "answers": [ "行事","ぎょうじ" ], "comment": "行事 (ぎょうじ): event, function" },
		{ "question": "行楽真地科", "answers": [ "行楽地","こうらくち" ], "comment": "行楽地 (こうらくち): tourist resort, holiday resort" },
		{ "question": "行流念真芸", "answers": [ "流行","はやり","りゅうこう" ], "comment": "流行 (はやり, りゅうこう): fashion, fad, vogue, craze, prevalence (e.g. of a disease), fashion, fad, vogue, craze, prevalence (e.g. of a disease)" },
		{ "question": "行親足科歩", "answers": [ "歩行","ほこう","かち" ], "comment": "歩行 (ほこう, かち): walk, foot soldier (Edo period), samurai on foot, going on foot, walking" },
		{ "question": "術事音火春", "answers": [ "火事","かじ" ], "comment": "火事 (かじ): fire, conflagration" },
		{ "question": "術会立後間", "answers": [ "術後","じゅつご" ], "comment": "術後 (じゅつご): postoperative" },
		{ "question": "術写地春道", "answers": [ "地道","じみち" ], "comment": "地道 (じみち): steady, honest, sober, straightforward" },
		{ "question": "術出場声月", "answers": [ "出場","しゅつじょう","でば" ], "comment": "出場 (しゅつじょう, でば): (stage) appearance, performance, participation (e.g. in a tournament), one's time (e.g. to go on stage), one's turn, source, origin, place of production" },
		{ "question": "術名作事明", "answers": [ "名作","めいさく" ], "comment": "名作 (めいさく): masterpiece" },
		{ "question": "術地時芸言", "answers": [ "芸術","げいじゅつ" ], "comment": "芸術 (げいじゅつ): (fine) art, the arts" },
		{ "question": "術年言半色", "answers": [ "半年","はんとし","はんねん" ], "comment": "半年 (はんとし, はんねん): half year, half year" },
		{ "question": "術用見作音", "answers": [ "作用","さよう" ], "comment": "作用 (さよう): action, operation, effect, function" },
		{ "question": "見先草入車", "answers": [ "先入見","せんにゅうけん" ], "comment": "先入見 (せんにゅうけん): preconception, prejudice, preoccupation" },
		{ "question": "見前新給所", "answers": [ "所見","しょけん","見所","みどころ","けんじょ","けんしょ" ], "comment": "所見 (しょけん): view, opinion, finding, findings\n見所 (みどころ, けんじょ, けんしょ): point worthy of note, highlight (e.g. in a film), thing to note, good prospects for the future, promise, audience seating (noh theater), audience (esp. in noh), audience seating (noh theater), audience (esp. in noh)" },
		{ "question": "見時音草月", "answers": [ "月見草","つきみそう" ], "comment": "月見草 (つきみそう): evening primrose (esp. the fourwing evening primrose, Oenothera tetraptera)" },
		{ "question": "見楽元王声", "answers": [ "声楽","せいがく" ], "comment": "声楽 (せいがく): vocal music" },
		{ "question": "見楽行命格", "answers": [ "行楽","こうらく" ], "comment": "行楽 (こうらく): outing, picnic, excursion, pleasure trip" },
		{ "question": "見空男肉本", "answers": [ "見本","みほん" ], "comment": "見本 (みほん): sample, specimen, pattern, model, example" },
		{ "question": "見雨園水身", "answers": [ "雨水","あまみず","うすい" ], "comment": "雨水 (あまみず, うすい): rain water, \"rain water\" solar term (approx. Feb 19), rain water, \"rain water\" solar term (approx. Feb 19)" },
		{ "question": "見雨念花命", "answers": [ "花見","はなみ" ], "comment": "花見 (はなみ): cherry blossom viewing, flower viewing" },
		{ "question": "親安入生写", "answers": [ "写生","しゃせい" ], "comment": "写生 (しゃせい): sketching, drawing from nature, portrayal, description" },
		{ "question": "親強足発時", "answers": [ "発足","ほっそく","はっそく" ], "comment": "発足 (ほっそく, はっそく): starting, inauguration, launch, founding, establishment, start-up, starting, inauguration, launch, founding, establishment, start-up" },
		{ "question": "親新音国会", "answers": [ "国会","こっかい" ], "comment": "国会 (こっかい): National Diet, parliament, congress" },
		{ "question": "親時面本番", "answers": [ "本番","ほんばん" ], "comment": "本番 (ほんばん): performance, take, going before an audience or on-air, game, season, crucial moment, actual sexual intercourse (i.e. not simulated), penetration" },
		{ "question": "言器道火見", "answers": [ "火器","かき" ], "comment": "火器 (かき): firearms, guns" },
		{ "question": "言園命歩学", "answers": [ "学園","がくえん" ], "comment": "学園 (がくえん): academy, campus" },
		{ "question": "言意王念合", "answers": [ "合意","ごうい" ], "comment": "合意 (ごうい): agreement, consent, mutual understanding, accord" },
		{ "question": "言明数風道", "answers": [ "言明","げんめい","明言","めいげん" ], "comment": "言明 (げんめい): declaration, statement, assertion\n明言 (めいげん): declaration, statement" },
		{ "question": "言気集水世", "answers": [ "水気","みずけ","すいき" ], "comment": "水気 (みずけ, すいき): moisture, dampness, vapor, vapour, dropsy, edema, oedema, moisture, dampness, vapor, vapour, dropsy, edema, oedema" },
		{ "question": "言間牛歩配", "answers": [ "牛歩","ぎゅうほ" ], "comment": "牛歩 (ぎゅうほ): snail's pace, slow progress" },
		{ "question": "記文科数新", "answers": [ "文科","ぶんか" ], "comment": "文科 (ぶんか): literary course, the arts" },
		{ "question": "記科地言中", "answers": [ "地中","ちちゅう" ], "comment": "地中 (ちちゅう): underground, subterranean" },
		{ "question": "記見意歩時", "answers": [ "意見","いけん" ], "comment": "意見 (いけん): opinion, view, comment" },
		{ "question": "記集人外進", "answers": [ "外人","がいじん","ほかびと","ガイジン","人外","じんがい","にんがい" ], "comment": "外人 (がいじん, ほかびと, ガイジン): foreigner (esp. one of European ancestry), gaijin, outsider, foreigner (esp. one of European ancestry), gaijin, outsider, foreigner (esp. one of European ancestry), gaijin, outsider\n人外 (じんがい, にんがい): uninhabited area, acting inhumanly, inhuman person, nonhuman life (usu. sentient), uninhabited area, acting inhumanly, inhuman person, nonhuman life (usu. sentient)" },
		{ "question": "足写物記体", "answers": [ "物体","ぶったい","もったい" ], "comment": "物体 (ぶったい, もったい): body, object, superior airs, air of importance, overemphasis" },
		{ "question": "足肉夜手物", "answers": [ "手足","てあし" ], "comment": "手足 (てあし): one's hands and feet, limbs" },
		{ "question": "足進気器配", "answers": [ "気配","けはい","きはい" ], "comment": "気配 (けはい, きはい): indication, sign, hint, presence, trend, quotation (esp. stock market), indication, sign, hint, presence, trend, quotation (esp. stock market)" },
		{ "question": "身場時元行", "answers": [ "身元","みもと" ], "comment": "身元 (みもと): person's identity, ID, past, background" },
		{ "question": "身物学力格", "answers": [ "学力","がくりょく","力学","りきがく" ], "comment": "学力 (がくりょく): scholarly ability, scholarship, knowledge, literary ability\n力学 (りきがく): mechanics, dynamics" },
		{ "question": "身長国春紙", "answers": [ "身長","しんちょう","長身","ちょうしん" ], "comment": "身長 (しんちょう): height (of body), stature\n長身 (ちょうしん): tall figure, high stature" },
		{ "question": "身音見所夜", "answers": [ "所見","しょけん","見所","みどころ","けんじょ","けんしょ" ], "comment": "所見 (しょけん): view, opinion, finding, findings\n見所 (みどころ, けんじょ, けんしょ): point worthy of note, highlight (e.g. in a film), thing to note, good prospects for the future, promise, audience seating (noh theater), audience (esp. in noh), audience seating (noh theater), audience (esp. in noh)" },
		{ "question": "車合世歩用", "answers": [ "歩合","ぶあい" ], "comment": "歩合 (ぶあい): rate, ratio, commission, percentage, poundage" },
		{ "question": "車念春声外", "answers": [ "外車","がいしゃ","車外","しゃがい" ], "comment": "外車 (がいしゃ): foreign automobile\n車外 (しゃがい): outside a car" },
		{ "question": "車発真草分", "answers": [ "発車","はっしゃ" ], "comment": "発車 (はっしゃ): departure of a vehicle" },
		{ "question": "車道園徒強", "answers": [ "車道","しゃどう" ], "comment": "車道 (しゃどう): roadway" },
		{ "question": "進入足番明", "answers": [ "進入","しんにゅう" ], "comment": "進入 (しんにゅう): entry, approach, penetration" },
		{ "question": "進手雨名身", "answers": [ "名手","めいしゅ" ], "comment": "名手 (めいしゅ): master, expert, expert board game player (chess, go, shogi, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "進楽手場紙", "answers": [ "手紙","てがみ" ], "comment": "手紙 (てがみ): letter" },
		{ "question": "進牛国外内", "answers": [ "国内外","こくないがい" ], "comment": "国内外 (こくないがい): domestic and foreign, inside and outside the country" },
		{ "question": "進紙月大空", "answers": [ "大空","おおぞら" ], "comment": "大空 (おおぞら): heavens, firmament, sky" },
		{ "question": "進間心春身", "answers": [ "心身","身心","しんしん","しんじん" ], "comment": "心身 (しんしん, しんじん): mind and body, mind and body\n身心 (しんしん, しんじん): mind and body, mind and body" },
		{ "question": "道中写器水", "answers": [ "中水道","ちゅうすいどう" ], "comment": "中水道 (ちゅうすいどう): gray-water system, grey-water system, recycled waste-water" },
		{ "question": "道安時実中", "answers": [ "ちゅうどう","道中","どうちゅう","中道","なかみち" ], "comment": "中道 (ちゅうどう): middle of the road, moderation, golden mean, the middle (of what one is doing), half-way, middle way, middle path\n道中 (どうちゅう): along the way, journey\n中道 (なかみち): road through the middle, middle road" },
		{ "question": "道理時写言", "answers": [ "道理","どうり" ], "comment": "道理 (どうり): reason, truth" },
		{ "question": "道目時配歩", "answers": [ "歩道","ほどう" ], "comment": "歩道 (ほどう): footpath, walkway, sidewalk" },
		{ "question": "道記数文作", "answers": [ "作文","さくぶん","さくもん" ], "comment": "作文 (さくぶん, さくもん): writing (an essay, prose, etc.), composition, formal writing with little real meaning, writing (poetry), composing" },
		{ "question": "配代半心事", "answers": [ "心配事","しんぱいごと" ], "comment": "心配事 (しんぱいごと): worries, cares, troubles" },
		{ "question": "配力強用女", "answers": [ "強力","きょうりょく","ごうりき" ], "comment": "強力 (きょうりょく, ごうりき): powerful, strong, herculean strength, mountain carrier-guide" },
		{ "question": "配男学出術", "answers": [ "学術","がくじゅつ" ], "comment": "学術 (がくじゅつ): science, learning, scholarship, arts and sciences, academic pursuits" },
		{ "question": "重前事安念", "answers": [ "事前","じぜん" ], "comment": "事前 (じぜん): prior, beforehand, in advance, before the fact, ex ante" },
		{ "question": "重大歩見写", "answers": [ "重大","じゅうだい" ], "comment": "重大 (じゅうだい): serious, important, significant, grave, weighty" },
		{ "question": "重後強体会", "answers": [ "体重","たいじゅう","重体","じゅうたい" ], "comment": "体重 (たいじゅう): body weight, one's weight\n重体 (じゅうたい): seriously ill, serious condition, critical state" },
		{ "question": "重白明入間", "answers": [ "明白","めいはく","あからさま" ], "comment": "明白 (めいはく, あからさま): obvious, clear, plain, evident, apparent, explicit, overt, plain, frank, candid, open, direct, straightforward, unabashed, blatant, flagrant" },
		{ "question": "重色記親交", "answers": [ "親交","しんこう" ], "comment": "親交 (しんこう): intimacy, friendship, friendly relations" },
		{ "question": "重術和月先", "answers": [ "先月","せんげつ" ], "comment": "先月 (せんげつ): last month" },
		{ "question": "長代体水見", "answers": [ "体長","たいちょう" ], "comment": "体長 (たいちょう): length of an animal (sometimes including and sometimes excluding the tail)" },
		{ "question": "長作明園肉", "answers": [ "園長","えんちょう" ], "comment": "園長 (えんちょう): head of a garden, kindergarten principal, nursery school principal, park director (botanical garden), zoo director (zoological garden), head of a plantation" },
		{ "question": "長内徒牛科", "answers": [ "内科","ないか" ], "comment": "内科 (ないか): internal medicine, i.e. treatment by medical procedures rather than surgical procedures, department of internal medicine (hospital, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "長器世所白", "answers": [ "所長","しょちょう","長所","ちょうしょ" ], "comment": "所長 (しょちょう): chief, head (of an office, of a laboratory)\n長所 (ちょうしょ): strong point, merit, virtue, advantage" },
		{ "question": "長場合花明", "answers": [ "場合","ばあい" ], "comment": "場合 (ばあい): case, situation" },
		{ "question": "長安地女進", "answers": [ "長女","ちょうじょ" ], "comment": "長女 (ちょうじょ): eldest daughter, first-born daughter" },
		{ "question": "長念名食地", "answers": [ "地名","ちめい" ], "comment": "地名 (ちめい): place name" },
		{ "question": "長水色徒意", "answers": [ "水色","みずいろ" ], "comment": "水色 (みずいろ): light blue" },
		{ "question": "長芸力安用", "answers": [ "安芸","あき" ], "comment": "安芸 (あき): former name of Hiroshima prefecture" },
		{ "question": "長雨事親真", "answers": [ "長雨","ながあめ","ながめ" ], "comment": "長雨 (ながあめ, ながめ): long spell of rain, long spell of rain" },
		{ "question": "間中徒場白", "answers": [ "間中","あいだじゅう","中間","ちゅうかん","ちゅうげん" ], "comment": "間中 (あいだじゅう): during\n中間 (ちゅうかん, ちゅうげん): middle, midway, interim, samurai's attendant, footman" },
		{ "question": "間分意目術", "answers": [ "分間","ふんかん" ], "comment": "分間 (ふんかん): minutes (period of)" },
		{ "question": "間国所先進", "answers": [ "先進国","せんしんこく" ], "comment": "先進国 (せんしんこく): advanced (developed) country, advanced nations" },
		{ "question": "間場長火時", "answers": [ "長時間","ちょうじかん" ], "comment": "長時間 (ちょうじかん): long period of time, long playing" },
		{ "question": "間実命空徒", "answers": [ "実空間","じつくうかん" ], "comment": "実空間 (じつくうかん): position space (quantum mechanics), real space" },
		{ "question": "間強中見理", "answers": [ "間中","あいだじゅう","中間","ちゅうかん","ちゅうげん" ], "comment": "間中 (あいだじゅう): during\n中間 (ちゅうかん, ちゅうげん): middle, midway, interim, samurai's attendant, footman" },
		{ "question": "間後実大国", "answers": [ "国大","こくだい","大国","たいこく" ], "comment": "国大 (こくだい): national university\n大国 (たいこく): large country, major powers" },
		{ "question": "間時長見親", "answers": [ "長時間","ちょうじかん" ], "comment": "長時間 (ちょうじかん): long period of time, long playing" },
		{ "question": "間発名後肉", "answers": [ "後発","こうはつ" ], "comment": "後発 (こうはつ): starting late" },
		{ "question": "間身春給合", "answers": [ "間合","まあい","合間","あいま" ], "comment": "間合 (まあい): interval, distance, break, pause, suitable time, appropriate opportunity, distance between opponents (kendo)\n合間 (あいま): interval, break, pause, spare moment" },
		{ "question": "間風楽心力", "answers": [ "風力","ふうりょく" ], "comment": "風力 (ふうりょく): wind power, force (level on the Beaufort wind speed scale)" },
		{ "question": "集前間和出", "answers": [ "出前","でまえ","前出","ぜんしゅつ" ], "comment": "出前 (でまえ): catering, meal delivery service\n前出 (ぜんしゅつ): aforementioned, discussed above, former, previous" },
		{ "question": "集草世出間", "answers": [ "出世間","しゅっせけん" ], "comment": "出世間 (しゅっせけん): monastic life" },
		{ "question": "集重念物事", "answers": [ "事物","じぶつ","物事","ものごと" ], "comment": "事物 (じぶつ): things, affairs\n物事 (ものごと): things, everything" },
		{ "question": "雨世元体年", "answers": [ "元年","がんねん" ], "comment": "元年 (がんねん): first year (of a specific reign)" },
		{ "question": "雨出紙進元", "answers": [ "進出","しんしゅつ" ], "comment": "進出 (しんしゅつ): advance (into a new market or stage of progress), launching (a new career or venture), expanding (into a new market), stepping forward, emerging" },
		{ "question": "雨命入配分", "answers": [ "配分","はいぶん","分配","ぶんぱい" ], "comment": "配分 (はいぶん): distribution, allotment\n分配 (ぶんぱい): division, splitting, sharing, distribution, dissemination, allocation" },
		{ "question": "雨数言人元", "answers": [ "数人","すうにん","人数","にんずう","ひとかず","にんず" ], "comment": "数人 (すうにん): several people\n人数 (にんずう, ひとかず, にんず): the number of people, many people, a large number of people, the number of people, many people, a large number of people, the number of people, many people, a large number of people" },
		{ "question": "雨新心王真", "answers": [ "真心","まごころ","まこころ" ], "comment": "真心 (まごころ, まこころ): sincerity, devotion, sincerity, devotion" },
		{ "question": "雨日園記術", "answers": [ "日記","にっき" ], "comment": "日記 (にっき): diary, journal" },
		{ "question": "雨発草先合", "answers": [ "先発","せんぱつ" ], "comment": "先発 (せんぱつ): starting in advance, starting first, going first, going ahead, starting (in team sports)" },
		{ "question": "面命新火会", "answers": [ "面会","めんかい" ], "comment": "面会 (めんかい): meeting (face-to-face), interview" },
		{ "question": "面女番水念", "answers": [ "水面","すいめん","みなも" ], "comment": "水面 (すいめん, みなも): water's surface, water's surface" },
		{ "question": "面安力王出", "answers": [ "出力","しゅつりょく" ], "comment": "出力 (しゅつりょく): output (electrical, signal, etc.)" },
		{ "question": "面所夜春名", "answers": [ "名所","めいしょ","などころ" ], "comment": "名所 (めいしょ, などころ): famous place, name of a part (of an instrument, etc.), name and address, famous place, name of a part (of an instrument, etc.), name and address" },
		{ "question": "面春学大流", "answers": [ "大学","だいがく" ], "comment": "大学 (だいがく): post-secondary education institution, incl. university, college, etc., former central university of Kyoto (established under the ritsuryo system for the training of government administrators), the Great Learning (one of the Four Books)" },
		{ "question": "面紙作番牛", "answers": [ "紙面","しめん" ], "comment": "紙面 (しめん): space (page)" },
		{ "question": "面肉歩入流", "answers": [ "流入","りゅうにゅう" ], "comment": "流入 (りゅうにゅう): afflux, influx" },
		{ "question": "面行雨花進", "answers": [ "行進","こうしん","進行","しんこう" ], "comment": "行進 (こうしん): march, parade\n進行 (しんこう): moving forward (e.g. vehicle), onward movement, advance (work, procedure, etc), advancement, progress, progress (of a disease), disease progression, progression (harmonic, melodic)" },
		{ "question": "面見前新安", "answers": [ "前面","ぜんめん","面前","めんぜん" ], "comment": "前面 (ぜんめん): front part, frontage, facade, initial pledge (e.g. election), opening slogan\n面前 (めんぜん): presence" },
		{ "question": "面配出身写", "answers": [ "出身","しゅっしん" ], "comment": "出身 (しゅっしん): person's origin (e.g. city, country, parentage, school)" },
		{ "question": "面集手給間", "answers": [ "手間","てま" ], "comment": "手間 (てま): time, labour, labor" },
		{ "question": "面集風実名", "answers": [ "実名","じつめい","名実","めいじつ" ], "comment": "実名 (じつめい): real name\n名実 (めいじつ): in name and in reality, nominally and virtually, form and contents" },
		{ "question": "音園入春真", "answers": [ "入園","にゅうえん" ], "comment": "入園 (にゅうえん): enrollment in kindergarten, enrolment in kindergarten, entering a park, garden, zoo, etc." },
		{ "question": "音学交目物", "answers": [ "物音","ものおと","音物","いんもつ","いんぶつ" ], "comment": "物音 (ものおと): sounds\n音物 (いんもつ, いんぶつ): present (to build up a \"friendship\" with someone), bribe, present (to build up a \"friendship\" with someone), bribe" },
		{ "question": "音理配生学", "answers": [ "生理学","せいりがく" ], "comment": "生理学 (せいりがく): physiology" },
		{ "question": "音生春草人", "answers": [ "人生","じんせい" ], "comment": "人生 (じんせい): (human) life (i.e. conception to death)" },
		{ "question": "音白目男世", "answers": [ "目白","めじろ","メジロ","白目","しろめ" ], "comment": "目白 (めじろ, メジロ): white-eye family of birds (Zosteropidae), Japanese white-eye (Zosterops japonicus), white-eye family of birds (Zosteropidae), Japanese white-eye (Zosterops japonicus)\n白目 (しろめ, しろめ): white of the eye, cold, unwelcoming eyes, white of the eye, cold, unwelcoming eyes, pewter, solder, pewter, solder, pewter, solder, pewter, solder" },
		{ "question": "音真目配面", "answers": [ "真面目","しんめんもく","しんめんぼく","まじめ" ], "comment": "真面目 (しんめんもく, しんめんぼく, まじめ): one's true character, one's true self, oneself, seriousness, earnestness, one's true character, one's true self, oneself, seriousness, earnestness, diligent, serious, honest, sober, grave, earnest, steady" },
		{ "question": "風交時理地", "answers": [ "地理","ちり" ], "comment": "地理 (ちり): geography" },
		{ "question": "風器安年代", "answers": [ "年代","ねんだい" ], "comment": "年代 (ねんだい): age, era, period, date" },
		{ "question": "風地術生科", "answers": [ "生地","きじ","せいち" ], "comment": "生地 (きじ, せいち): cloth, fabric, material, texture, one's true character, unglazed pottery, uncooked dough, batter, birthplace" },
		{ "question": "風間念格身", "answers": [ "風格","ふうかく" ], "comment": "風格 (ふうかく): personality, style, appearance" },
		{ "question": "食半配用行", "answers": [ "食用","しょくよう" ], "comment": "食用 (しょくよう): for use as food, edible" },
		{ "question": "食和科交雨", "answers": [ "和食","わしょく" ], "comment": "和食 (わしょく): Japanese food, Japanese-style meal, Japanese cuisine" },
		{ "question": "食器雨年歩", "answers": [ "食器","しょっき" ], "comment": "食器 (しょっき): tableware" },
		{ "question": "食園王車給", "answers": [ "給食","きゅうしょく" ], "comment": "給食 (きゅうしょく): provision of lunch (e.g. at office, school, etc.), providing a meal, lunch service" },
		{ "question": "食新真念外", "answers": [ "外食","がいしょく" ], "comment": "外食 (がいしょく): eating out" },
		{ "question": "食番交心半", "answers": [ "交番","こうばん" ], "comment": "交番 (こうばん): police box, small neighborhood police station, alternation, alternating (e.g. current)" },
		{ "question": "食科進見道", "answers": [ "食道","しょくどう" ], "comment": "食道 (しょくどう): esophagus, gullet, esophageal" },
		{ "question": "食肉身芸雨", "answers": [ "食肉","しょくにく","肉食","にくしょく" ], "comment": "食肉 (しょくにく): meat (for consumption)\n肉食 (にくしょく): meat eating, eating of meat, meat diet, carnivorous" }
	]
}
